<Document>
  # Jobs

  SS14 normally contains many jobs, traditionally split into seven major departments.
  On Frontier Station those distinctions are smaller and often not relevant - there isn't a single central station, and a single shuttle can perform multiple functions.

  Below are some example jobs you can play. Frontier is an open-ended, roleplay-heavy server: jobs are guidelines, not strict limits. One of Frontier's strengths is that the job you pick won't lock you out of doing other things.

  ## Frontier
  [color=#b18644]Frontier[/color] is closest to Service on a traditional station: these roles focus on helping people across the sector - delivering mail, handling logistics, or keeping the usually quiet Frontier Outpost running.

  This department also technically contains two department heads: the Station Representative and the Director of Care. See their individual guidebook entries for details. In short: the Station Representative keeps the Outpost moving, and the Director of Care heads medical operations.

  ## New Frontier Sheriff's Department (NFSD)
  [color=#b18644]NFSD[/color] is the Frontier Sector's security force. Headed by the Sheriff, they maintain order, protect shuttles from pirates, and watch for Syndicate activity. Expect lawkeeping, bounty work, and occasional firefights.

  ## Civilian
  [color=#b18644]Civilian[/color] is where most players will be. Common civilian roles include:

  - Contractors - follow the money: take jobs, complete objectives, and earn credits. Become the richest person in the sector.
  - Mercenaries - join dangerous expeditions for rare loot. High risk, high reward.
  - Pilots - operate ships: pilot your shuttle, evade pirates, and [italic]don’t[/italic] hit asteroids.

  Note: there is little mechanical difference in what you can do in-game based on your civilian role. Much of your gameplay is determined by the ship you pilot, not the role you spawn with.

  ## Engineering
  [color=#b18644]Engineering[/color] includes the Plant Manager and Plant Technicians. They run the Edison Power Plant, generating the sector's (sometimes unreasonable) amounts of power. Someone has to fuel the sun...

  ## The Frontier Sector
  As mentioned earlier, what you do in a round depends more on the shuttle you fly than the job you start with. Want to be a chef? Pick up a Ceres and cook. You don't have to (or more precisely: you cannot) start as a chef - create your own destiny.
</Document>
