<Document>
# Medical Bounties

With space being as dangerous as it is on the Frontier, NT has created an initiative to reward retrieving, healing, and transporting valuable corpses back to medical facilities on inner worlds.

Remember, 70% of your value is in your biogenetic IP!

## Finding Bounties

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicalPod"/>
</Box>

These life-saving emergency pods can be found on [color=#88b0d1]ship wreckage[/color]. Each emergency pod comes equipped with [color=#ffff00]blinking indicators[/color]. You can see these at a glance in the dark, and they have an distinct [color=#80b9c4]health analyzer[/color] display on the side.

These pods tend to be anchored to their ship, but they are [bold]heavy[/bold]. If needed, the occupant can be ejected and brought into safety quickly. Remember, they're still vulnerable to barotrauma.

## Recovering Bounties

In order to safely transport the bodies, [bold]before the bounty can be redeemed, they must first be resuscitated back to health[/bold].  Ensure that the body is alive, stable and breathing. [color=#00ffff]Cryogenic[/color] medications used in cryo pods are recommended for cases with extreme damage for efficient use of resources.

## Claiming Bounties

Once the bountied asset is stable, they'll likely remain in a catatonic state. Don't worry, this is normal, and you will not be held liable for malpractice.

When you are ready to redeem the bounty, return the asset to the nearest [color=#469bbd]body retrieval unit[/color]. Simply insert the revived asset into the unit. [color=#d40606]Both lights[/color] should be on. Open the panel on the unit and hit the "Redeem" button, and enjoy the hard-earned spesos.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineMedicalBountyRedemption"/>
</Box>

## History

Starting in 2472, safety initiatives within Nanotrasen promoted the creation of LifeSavior emergency medical pods, for use in catastrophic incidents aboard stations and shuttles. This initiative ended two years ago due to mounting pressure over unfounded, unprovable claims that emergency pod-based fatalities outnumbered saved lives by 5:1.

</Document>
