<Document>
# 13. Command Standards

You are the highest authority in the sector apart from Central Command. You must act as an example for the rest of the community.

    - Command roles (e.g. Station Rep, Sheriff) are held to a much higher standard of roleplay.
    - Command is [color=#ff0000]required[/color] to maintain pay for their respective staff as a part of their job.
    -- You are expected to maintain pay for roles absent other command positions, within reason.
    -- Minimum hourly pay rates are $10,000 for station crew, $20,000 for Station Rep and Sheriff, and $15,000 for security.
    -- Embezzlement of station funds is strictly forbidden.
    - If ending your shift early:
    -- Have your ID on your character.
    -- Reopen your position at the station records computer.
    -- Return to cryosleep.
    -- If you cannot (disconnect, crash, power outage, etc.), ping the game admins in Discord.
    -- Ensure you open your job slot prior to going to cryo.
    -- You are welcome to open that slot early in order for a new SR or Sheriff to join so you can provide a briefing to them beforehand.
    -- Ahelp if you are unable to pay your staff prior to going to cryo.
    - Command is expected to enforce docking laws and collect any fines related to dock loitering.
    -- Refer to Space Law for the specific laws on dock loitering.
    -- Funds collected from this may be used for station payroll or station supplies.
    -- Traffic to and from traffic-controlled stations should be kept flowing.
    - You may not tax, lease, rent, or otherwise impede the use of station resources. This includes:
    -- Charging docking fees.
    -- Granting docking extensions.
    -- Restricting vendor access (e.g. placing machines behind locked doors).
    -- Restricting access to station resources.
    - The Sheriff or SR are under no obligation to offer to purchase contraband from other players. Seizure of illegal goods is always allowed under Space Law.
    -- If contraband buy-backs or contraband hunting schemes are to be offered, how they are conducted is at the discretion of the SR or Sheriff.
    -- Admins will not grant compensation to players for contraband which is seized by the authorities.
    - The Sheriff is to ensure that any recruited cadets receive proper training and are supervised properly at all times.
    -- Cadets should be working alongside the Sheriff or assigned to a suitably experienced officer who can oversee their training as an officer and in Space Law, SOP and the server rules relating to the NFSD.
    -- Cadets who refuse training, try to farm playtime or insist on working alone can face consequences IC or be ahelped for their actions.
    -- Repeated incidents may be considered a sign of poor leadership. Cadets are your responsibility.
</Document>
