<Document>
  #Frontier Station Rules, v5

  ##Recent Changes
  - Rules reformatted for the guidebook.

  [color=red]These rules are expected to be read in their entirety.[/color]

  ##Admin Decisions
  - All admin decisions are final.
  - Rules are enforced to the spirit of the rules and subject to admin interpretation.
  - Admins may disregard any/all rules if they deem it in the best interest of the current round, the server, and/or the community.
  - Admins are accountable for their actions. Abuse of admin privileges will be dealt with by staff.

  ##General Information
  - Disconnecting from or ignoring/evading admin-helps will result in an appeal-only ban.
  - Staff is not obligated to cover player losses, deaths or delays.
  -- This includes, but is not limited to: ship deeds, money, respawns and revivals.
  -- Any action taken is at the staff's discretion, and depends on the circumstances.

  # Rule List

  All of the below rules apply at all times, including between rounds.

  ## Zero Tolerance Rules
  You are liable to be banned without previous warning for breaking these rules.
  - [textlink="Click here to read the zero tolerance rules." link="FrontierRuleZeroTolerance"]

  ## Core Rules
  These are the general rules of Frontier. Click them for more information.
  - [textlink="1. Don't be a dick." link="FrontierRule1"]
  - [textlink="2. Don't act on out of character info." link="FrontierRule2"]
  - [textlink="3. Don't attack another player without reasonable escalation." link="FrontierRule3"]
  - [textlink="4. Use chat for chat, and communicate in English." link="FrontierRule4"]

  ## Roleplay Rules
  These are the roleplay rules of Frontier. Click them for more information.
  - [textlink="5. Your character should be plausible, and is separate from you." link="FrontierRule5"]
  - [textlink="6. Don't fight near Frontier Outpost." link="FrontierRule6"]
  - [textlink="7. Antagonists and non-antags are enemies." link="FrontierRule7"]
  - [textlink="8. PvP combat is allowed, but subject to escalation." link="FrontierRule8"]
  - [textlink="9. Pirates must follow their code." link="FrontierRule9"]
  - [textlink="10. Non-capital Space Law offenses may be committed with good reason." link="FrontierRule10"]
  - [textlink="11. Silicons must follow their laws." link="FrontierRule11"]

  ## NFSD and Command
  These rules also apply to any individual who is deputized or is acting in the place of a NFSD/Command role.
  - [textlink="12. Security and Station staff must act with integrity." link="FrontierRule12"]
  - [textlink="13. Command staff must act with integrity." link="FrontierRule13"]

</Document>
