<Document>

  # New Frontiers definitions and terms

This section will explain most the common terminology used on the server both in character and out of character.

  ## Panic Bunker
  Server tool that does not let in account with less than 10 hours of gameplay into the server if there is no admin present, one of the most effective tools up to this date to avoid the constant stream of raiders and griefers into the server.

  ## Raider
  Organized group of online people with the intention to break the server rules, ruin your round or just kill your character with no intention to RP, be armed and prepared to defend yourself and contact admins trough Ahelp to report and ban them.

  ## Ahelp
  Short for Admin Help, can be accessed via F1 to directly contact with the server moderation team to report issues, ask for advise or help.

  ## LTAP
  Leaving To Avoid Punishment refers to leaving the game in the middle of an ahelp inquiry started by the admins, while being forced to read the rules or leaving the server on a constant basis after being arrested by the NFSD for commiting a crime. [color=red]Doing this will lead to a ban or make it more severe.[/color]

  ## Levels of chat
  - IC (In Character): All conversation in world and in game, taking into consideration the lore and rp other players are having.
  - OOC (Out Of Character): All conversation with knowledge outside the game and themes that do not take inside the game universe (disabled mid round).
  - LOOC (Local Out Of Character): Same as OOC but spans the range of only your character.

  ## Metacommunications
  The sharing of ingame information trough outside communications like VC(Voice Chat), discord or any other means, be it for the means of cheating the game or to teach someone.

  ## POI
  Acronym for Point Of Interest, it is used for every station that spawns at the start of the round and acts as a meeting point where shuttles can dock at, examples being Tinnia's, Frontier Outpost, The Pit, Medical Dispatch and so on.

  ## Safezone
  The area encircling the Frontier Outpost with a span of 200m from the center of the station, completely invulnerable and with a pacification field for anyone under 10 hours of gameplay.

  ## Powergaming
  A display of consistent pattern of antisocial and unsporting behavior in which a player prioritizes their game experience at the expense of others through routine optimization and abuse of game mechanics/knowledge.

  ## Highgrading
  Refers to the act of buying ships, stripping its machinery or cutting out sections to merge it all together into a single vessel with the intention to bypass interacting with other player's ships to obtain resources/tech/food effectively trying to obtain everything on the game alone.

  ## SSD (Sudden Sleep Disease)
  IC term for going AFK or disconnecting from the game, it is considered for them to still be alive and should be roleplayed as any sleeping being.

  ## NFSD
  Acronym for the New Frontiers Sheriff Department, the policing force of the sector that counters the pirates and upholds the order.

  ## Space Law
  The system of rules that character have to follow IC depending on their role and affiliation, can be broken with exceptions, for more information consult rules section on [textlink="Crimes" link="FrontierRule10"].

  ## NFZ (No Fly Zone)
  Term often used by the NFSD to impose a restricted imaginary area on space with a determined range from there it is not permitted to go into without a permission.

  ## UIV
  Unidentified Vessel, a ship with no designation that is part of either a criminal or more dangerous organization not affiliated with Nanotrasen.

  ## Centcom
  Central command is considered the headquarters of Nanotrasen, the company that invested and has influence over the sector, often usually used to refer to the admins IC by saying "im faxing/messaging centcom".


</Document>
