  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerMedical" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingCloakCmo" Caption="Director of Care"
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerMedical" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

[color=Aqua]The Director of Care[/color] is responsible for keeping the sector [color=Green]healthy[/color]. A decent DoC makes sure emergency response medics get [color=Gold]paid[/color], a great one makes sure no one stays dead long enough to [color=Red]rot[/color].

Like all command, the [color=LightSeaGreen]DOC[/color] is a whitelist role, and so you're expected to know how the game works, and preferably how medics operate from experience.

# DoC Basics 
The DoC has a few specific tools available to them that need explaining.

## Medical Dispatch
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerMedical" Caption=""
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineMedicalBountyRedemption" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerMedical" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
The station itself is one of your most [color=LawnGreen]important tools[/color]. While it's built more as a waystation than a hospital, it's very common for people to come there for medical help, and The bar is a common point for people to gather at the end of their shifts. 

As the only place to buy [color=Aqua]medical ships[/color], you'll get a lot of people coming through to pick up a ship for [color=Turquoise]medical hybrid[/color] work.

Most importantly, there's an empty room right next to the [color=RoyalBlue]DoC's[/color] office for you to do whatever you want with. Many [color=RoyalBlue]DoCs[/color] use this room as a [color=CornflowerBlue]cryomed lab[/color], others use it as a [color=Aqua]clinic[/color], a botany bay, really anything you'd like to use it for. 

You have the authority to use these as you see fit, which often means making a nice little [color=DodgerBlue]hospital room[/color] to do cryo bounties in.

In general, you have the authority to make any changes you'd like to MD, as long as the changes you make don't disrupt the basic functions of the station. 

Be cautious before making an addition that might [color=Red]take away[/color] business from other roles, like a functioning kitchen or publicly available research server.

# Command Storage Cabinet
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Rack" Caption=""
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasThermoMachineFreezerFlatpack" Caption="Freezer Flatpack"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CryoPodFlatpack" Caption="Cryo-Pod Flatpack"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineRestockBooze" Caption=" Booze-O-Mat Restock Box"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Rack" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
There are supplies provided to you to build this out; there's a [color=DarkBlue]Command-locked room[/color] behind the Janitor's closet at one end of the station where you can find a cryotube and freezer flatpack, as well as an empty chem dispenser and a several crates full of various resources. 

## The DoC's Office
The DoC has a number of consoles in their office that help them do the various functions of their job.

## Station Administration
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTabletopStationAdminBankATMMedical" Caption="Station Administration "
  </Box>
[color=RoyalBlue]The Station Administration console[/color] is your station [color=Gold]bank account[/color]. You are generally allowed to use it as you see fit, as long as you do so reasonably. The definition of "reasonable" is intentionally vague, but part of getting whitelisted is the admins and community in general trusting your judgement and roleplay sense. So [color=Green]trust yourself[/color]; if you think an expense is reasonable, it probably is.

To withdraw, put an amount to withdraw, pick the reason closest to what you're withdrawing it for, give a short description of what you're getting it for, and click Withdraw. The admins will check these sometimes, but as long as you're doing something reasonable there won't be an issue. Taking 10,000 spesos for "Buying food" is [color=LightSeaGreen]fine[/color], taking 1,000,000 spesos for "funny clown show" probably [color=Red]isn't[/color].

To deposit, insert spesos just like you would for an ATM, and fill out the deposit fields just like you would the withdrawal fields. 

## Announcement Console
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTabletopComms" Caption="Announcement Console"
  </Box>
[color=RoyalBlue]The Announcement Console[/color] is used to send messages to the whole sector. Generally, you just enter your announcement in the field and click the "announce" button. The drop-down menu with colors is there to set the [color=Red]sector alert level[/color], you should not be editing that unless instructed to by the SR or Sheriff.

## MD shuttle console
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTabletopShuttle" Caption="MD shuttle console"
  </Box>
You also have a shuttle console for the MD itself. This works like a normal shuttle console, where you can undock ships, scan the sector, and keep an eye out for ship-based trouble. If you're coordinating medical response, you can use this to find out how far away different ships are to the alert using the map tab.

## Spare Consoles
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTabletopShuttle" Caption="MD shuttle console"
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTabletopComms" Caption="Announcement Console"
  </Box>
By default, you will spawn in with flatpacks for the Station Administration console and Announcement Console. These are also found in the DoC's office, but the ones you spawn in with can be brought aboard a ship that you buy and used to access these functions while away from MD. It's relatively common for DoCs to purchase a large ship to use as a mobile hospital, 

and these two consoles cover what you might need to not use MD at all.

## Your PDA
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DocPDA" Caption="MD shuttle console"
  </Box>
Your PDA has two functions not available to normal contractors.

The first is the [color=Gold]Spesoflow Lite app[/color]. This app lets you track your [color=LightGoldenRodYellow]budget[/color], showing you where money is coming in and being spent. Your budget will mostly come from [color=Green]Vaults[/color], [color=Red]Taxes[/color], and [color=Cyan]Medical Bounties[/color].

The second is Command Bounties. In the normal Bounty app, there's a second Command tab that is only available to Command personnel. You can use this to put up bounties for anything you need, and given the smaller number of people posting there, it'll remain more visible through the round. Remember to take down any bounties you put up before you cryo, though.

## DoC's Desk
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TableReinforced" Caption=""
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DocPDA" Caption="MD shuttle console"
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DocPDA" Caption="MD shuttle console"
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TableReinforced" Caption=""
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TableReinforced" Caption=""
  </Box>
It might sound weird to call out something that has little functional use, but the DoC's desk is great for interviews, medical debriefs, or just generally creating a [color=DarkBlue]professional atmosphere[/color] when you do business. If you're having people sign documents in person, or turn in slips, doing so at the desk, with two chairs facing each other, can heighten the immersion of the RP.

## Uniforms
In the small room you spawn in, there's a locker containing a medical director's hardsuit, as well as a number of pieces of clothing that are specific to the DoC. If you want to be easily recognized, wearing a distinctive hat and mantle is a great way to do that. Just be sure to [color=OrangeRed]bring it back[/color] before you cryo so the next DoC can use them if they want.

# DoC Duties
The Director of Care has much less strongly-defined duties than the SR or Sheriff. You are free to pursue the goal of making the sector healthier however you see fit. As a whitelisted player, you have the trust of the community and admin team to be able to run a department in a way that enhances the overall RP experience of the game, and this trust means that there are very few hard rules outside of the basic "pay people" and "don't do crime".

That said, there are a few common threads in how people play Director of Care.

## Authority
In short, your [color=SandyBrown]authority[/color] extends as far as the contracts you make. The only formal authority the DoC has is the authority to withdraw money from the station budget, and the authority to modify MD. The primary way you have to affect the sector is by hiring people to do medical work on your behalf, and issuing commands as allowed by that contractual relationship.

What this means is that your medical department is much more strongly influenced by your priorities than other departments might be. The SR and Sheriff have defaults for how many roles of each type can be played, and while some will adjust these numbers, it's much more rare for [color=Green]SRs[/color] and [color=RosyBrown]Sheriffs[/color] to actively recruit for their ranks in-round. Whereas no one spawns in as one of the DoC's employees, and everyone must be recruited manually.

## Staff
It's common for DoCs to seek out and hire a few emergency responders. 

Typically, these people will be [color=Gold]paid[/color] 15-20k/hr, with 10k as the minimum wage, like any paid role. Some DoCs will ask that responders collect [color=Green]signed receipts[/color] when they save someone as proof of work. 

Some DoCs will also give a bounty (typically in the 1-2k range) for each turned-in receipt. Some DoCs believe this encourages infighting among medics and don't offer a defined bounty. 

Even when there is no bounty, most DoCs appreciate being given signed healing receipts as proof that work was done. 

The precise amount given will depend on the medical budget that shift. Remember that it's better to offer a low salary and give a larger bonus than the other way around; if you're [color=Gold]flush with cash[/color] it's easy to spread, but if you're [color=Red]broke[/color] then you might not have the cash to pay everyone.

When you pay someone, it's generally good practice to round up to the nearest hour and note exactly which hours they're being paid for. 

So if someone is hired at 2:00 and cryos at 4:40, pay them [color=MediumPurple]three hours[/color] pay, up through 5:00. It's usually a good idea to pay a contractor what you owe them whenever they end up on station, just so you can pay in smaller chunks instead of one huge paycheck at the end. This will give you a better sense of what your [color=Gold]budget[/color] actually is. 

Sometimes you might have to [color=Red]fire someone[/color] if they're doing an exceptionally poor job, but even then you should always pay someone for the hours that they actually did work.

DoCs can also hire cryomed staff. One of the best ways for the MD to make money is turning in [color=RoyalBlue]cryo bounties[/color]. Any time a bounty is turned in, 75% of the listed value of the bounty is added to the [color=Gold]MD station account[/color]. 

When the DoC turns in the bounty, the listed value is also added to the [color=Gold]station account[/color], instead of being handed to the DoC as cash; resulting in [color=BlanchedAlmond]175%[/color] of the listed value being inserted into the account 

So whatever value you see for a medical bounty, add 75% for the total value of the bounty to the MD once turned in.

A typical [color=RoyalBlue]cryomed crew[/color] will be one [color=DarkOrange]chemist[/color], one [color=Lime]botanist[/color], and one or two [color=Moccasin]salvagers[/color]. The salvager(s) go out to find the medical pods. 

The [color=Lime]botanist[/color] will grow necessary plants (aloe and stellibinin are pretty vital), and the [color=DarkOrange]chemist[/color] will mix the chems and put them in the patient. Sometimes the DoC can take one or more of these roles, but a steady supply of bounty pods can more than pay for the cost of 3-4 employees.

If you're doing [color=RoyalBlue]cryomed bounties[/color], then you might need to buy more frozen bodies from people. It's relatively common to have an open bounty for medical bounties, so [color=Moccasin]salvagers[/color] who find them can get a better payout than they would selling them to Trade, and you can heal them and cash them in for a [color=Gold]profit[/color].

Around 5000 spesos is a typical bounty price (at the time of writing), which means that you'll likely make about 5000-10000 spesos from each healed body. 

You can put up these bounties in the normal bounty app, call them out on Common, or even holocall [color=Moccasin]salvager teams[/color] directly.

Sometimes a DoC will purchase a [color=Navy]large medical ship[/color] and operate out of there, using the station admin console and announcement console you spawn in with to access those functions while away from MD. 

Flying on a ship makes it much easier to find your own pods to heal, and gives you a lot more in the way of resources to heal people on the fly. On the other hand, it makes you a bit harder to find; Generally people expect to find the DoC at [color=Navy]MD[/color], and can get confused when you're not there.

## The Law
One important thing to note about your duties is that enforcing [color=OliveDrab]the law[/color] in general is [color=Red]NOT[/color] one of your duties. 

Enforcing [color=OliveDrab]Docking law[/color] specifically on MD is something you can do, though you'll need to call for a [color=Red]Guard[/color] or [color=OliveDrab]NFSD[/color] to come help if anyone is belligerent. 

As a member of command, you are never allowed to use [color=Red]C3 contraband[/color], cannot encourage anyone to pick up or use [color=Red]C3 contraband[/color], and cannot accept it as a gift except to immediately impound it for the NFSD to pick up later.
 
However, you are not required to actually enforce the law, including [color=Red]Contraband Possession[/color] law. 

You do not have the [color=OliveDrab]Authority[/color] to perform an arrest of any kind. If someone is breaking [color=OliveDrab]the law[/color] in your presence, you can ask them to stop or call the NFSD to come help, but you are not empowered to detain, search, or arrest even the most blatant of criminals. 

In particular, you should familiarize yourself with the [color=OliveDrab]Space Law[/color] around contraband chemicals. 

In general, chemicals that are mind-affecting are [color=OliveDrab]C2 Contraband[/color], and ones that mostly do damage or are otherwise very dangerous are [color=Red]C3 contraband[/color]. 

Be on the lookout for [color=Red]C3 Chemicals[/color], it's pretty common to be given large batches of random chems, and you shouldn't be keeping anything that's [color=Red]C3 contraband[/color].

Different DoCs have different policies for handling [color=LightCoral]law breaks[/color]. 

Some will call the [color=OliveDrab]NFSD[/color] every time with as much information as they can. 

Some will generally give a heads up that [color=Red]Contraband[/color] is floating around. 

Some will ignore breaches of [color=OliveDrab]the law[/color] that don't directly affect the overall health of the people in the sector. 

Remember that you're roleplaying a member of sector command, and that you should generally cooperate with the [color=OliveDrab]NFSD[/color] unless you have good in-round reason not to.
 
But you aren't required to know any [color=OliveDrab]Space Law[/color] outside the parts that reference the DoC directly, and can be pretty hands-off with other people breaking the law as long as you're not actively encouraging them.

## Paying Other Departments

Finally, as a member of [color=Blue]command[/color], you are encouraged by server rules to help pay FO/NFSD/PP staff if there is no corresponding [color=Blue]command[/color] member to pay already-hired staff members. 

You generally can't hire new staff (and you absolutely shouldn't be hiring Cadets or other NFSD personnel) but if someone has taken a default role or was hired by a since-cryo'd Command member, you should pay them from the appropriate station budget if you have the time to do so.
