<Document>
  # Salvage expeditions
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerSalvageExpedition"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TelecomServerFilledShuttle"/>
  </Box>
  Expeditions are adventures that you can do with your fellow crewmates or on your own. 

  You must pick a mission from the [color=#a4885c]salvage console[/color], each of which is of varying difficulty and reward.

  When you choose a mission, provided there are no other shuttles or objects nearby, the ship will immediately FTL jump to the mission area, if not you will have to move the ship further away first.

  Once you arrive, the chat will tell you which direction the target of the expedition is in.

  While planetside you will be unable to communicate via radio with the wider Frontier Sector, and unless you have a [color=#a4885c]telecommunication server[/color] installed you won't be able to use radio to communicate with your crew in the expedition either.

  # Being prepared
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobBloodCultistZealotMelee"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobFleshGolemExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobArgocyteEnforcerExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobCarpHoloExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobRogueSiliconHunter"/>
  </Box>
  During missions planetside, you will encounter dangers ranging from inhospitable environments to hostile wildlife and even blood-thirsty cultists or relentless automatons. If you want to survive and get off the planet richer than you were before you got to be prepared for the challenges ahead. You will need the right gear and the knowledge of how and when that gear should be used. And most importantly you will need the help of your crewmates.

  # Gear
  ## Environmental hazards
  The first thing you will encounter on the planet is The Planet itself. Environmental conditions on planets are diverse: not every planet has a breathable atmosphere or atmosphere at all and temperatures fluctuate significantly. The [color=#a4885c]salvage console[/color] will give you a rough idea of what conditions on the planet are in the [color=#a4885c]Modifiers[/color] section of the mission description. This information will help you to decide what environmental protection gear you need if you need any at all.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FloorLiquidPlasmaEntity"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FloorLavaEntity"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Biomes:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Grassland/Caves/Shadow:[/bold] no hazards have been observed so far.
  - [bold]Snow:[/bold] liquid plasma pools can be encountered in this biome. Touching one will result in setting self on fire.
  - [bold]Lava:[/bold] lava pools can be encountered in this biome. Touching one will result in setting self on fire.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingMaskGas"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirTankFilled"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Air quality modifiers:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]None:[/bold] the air is safe to breathe without internals on.
  - [bold]Dangerous atmosphere:[/bold] ranges from the toxic atmosphere to complete lack of it, requires internals toggled on at the very least and wearing sealed EVA or hardsuit in extreme cases.
  - [bold]Volatile atmosphere:[/bold] the atmosphere contains gaseous plasma in it. Requires internals on. Depending on what other gases are present, there is a distinct possibility of starting a plasma fire that will eventually engulf the entire planet.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterWinterMiner"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitEVA"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitBasic"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Temperature modifiers:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]None:[/bold] the temperatures on the planet are comfortable and no special equipment is needed.
  - [bold]Low temperature:[/bold] cold, but bearable unless you are a lizard (in that case wearing a winter coat or a hardsuit is advisable).
  - [bold]Extreme cold:[/bold] temperatures are close to absolute zero, so a hardsuit is required.
  - [bold]High temperature:[/bold] unpleasantly hot. 150 centigrade hot. Heat-resistant gear or a hardsuit is required.
  - [bold]Extreme heat:[/bold] temperatures are so high that wearing a hardsuit is mandatory.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Flare"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GlowstickBlue"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FlashlightLantern"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Floodlight"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Time of day:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Morning/Day/Evening times:[/bold] the ambient light on the planet is sufficient, no need for light sources.
  - [bold]Night time:[/bold] pitch black darkness, light sources are required for navigating the planet.
  
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Time constraints:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Rush:[/bold] you will have less time to complete the expedition. Set your priorities in advance.
  
  ## Tools
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Pickaxe"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Crowbar"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wrench"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Screwdriver"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wirecutter"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesGlassesMeson"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Welder"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Multitool"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RadioHandheld"/>
  </Box>
  Salvaging often requires digging through layers of rocks to reach an abandoned facility, deconstruction of various obstacles (like walls, and windows) to gain entrance to the ruins, prying open unpowered airlocks, or dismantling valuable machinery for ease of transportation. The tools will either make tasks easier (for example prying open airlocks with a crowbar is significantly faster than doing it by hand) or even possible in the first place (you need a mining tool to dig through rocks) or provide the means of communication between crewmates in absence of [color=#a4885c]telecommunication server[/color] (handheld radio).
  
  ## Medicine
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EmergencyMedipen"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Brutepack"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Ointment"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gauze"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicatedSuture"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RegenerativeMesh"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Tourniquet"/>
  </Box>
  You are going to get hurt. Period. Knowing the basics of medical care and having some medical supplies close at hand in time of need is the difference between life and death for you or your fellow crewmates. 
  
  Before embarking on an expedition consider stocking some medical supplies for the common damage types you are likely to receive ([color=red]brute[/color] and [color=#ffa500]burn[/color]) as well as tools for stopping [color=red]bleeding[/color], like [color=#a4885c]gauze[/color] or [color=#a4885c]emergency medipen[/color]. The most basic medications can be procured from vending machines, however, the advanced and more efficient ones are harder to obtain, but most of the time they can be bought from other players, providing medical services.
  
  Having medical tools at hand is half of the job: before going on an adventure be sure to learn the basics of medical care.
  
  ## Armor
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadHelmetBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterArmorBulletproof"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterArmorReflective"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RiotShield"/>
  </Box>
  Most of the time you won't be able to avoid getting hit. Wearing armor will lessen the blow to your health and it will allow you to remain in action for longer and might buy you enough time to apply medicine. Hostile entities in abandoned facilities deal various types of damage, so choosing your armor accordingly will increase your chances of survival dramatically.
  
  Here are some examples for your consideration:
  - [color=#a4885c]Syndicate naval forces[/color] use firearms that deal [color=yellow]pierce[/color] type of damage: wearing armor with high protection against this type of damage (like a bulletproof vest) will significantly reduce the damage you take;
  - [color=#a4885c]Rogue silicones[/color] primarily deal [color=#ffa500]heat[/color] type of damage: wearing a reflective vest is a good choice when facing rogue silicons.
  
  ## The Crew
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcGood"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcBad"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcUgly"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcThatGuy"/>
  </Box>
  By far your best bet at surviving the expeditions is your fellow crewmates: knowing how to medicate yourself is important, but you can't apply bandages if you are unconscious. 
  
  ## Know your enemy
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesHudMedical"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesHudDiagnostic"/>
  </Box>
  Adaptability is key: strategies and tactics that work against [color=#a4885c]xenos[/color] might not work at all against hostile [color=#a4885c]mercenaries[/color] and vice versa. Guidebook entries on hostile entities might give you a bit of an idea of what to expect planeside, however, those won't replace firsthand experience. Drop down to the planet, salvager, and brave the dangers, for the riches won't wait for you forever!
  
</Document>