<Document>
  # Salvage expeditions
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerSalvageExpedition"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TelecomServerFilledShuttle"/>
  </Box>
  
  Your ship will jump to a planet and you need to complete an objective in a limited time.[br][/br]
  When that time runs out, the ship jumps back, [bold]whether you're on it or not[/bold].

  Ships purchased at Frontier Outpost [bold]cannot[/bold] go on expedition, but [italic]any purchased at [bold]Expeditionary Lodge[/bold] can[/italic].
  You will need to use the [color=#a4885c]salvage console[/color] onboard.

  To go on an expedition:
  - Pilot your ship so there is 200 m of empty space in each direction.
  - Use the [color=#a4885c]salvage console[/color].
  - Pick one of the five missions offered to you.
  - Note the enemy, conditions, total time, and objectives for the mission.
  - Buckle into a seat to avoid falling down.

  Tips for expeditions:
  - Start with easier missions and progress to harder ones as you get better equipped.
  - Different enemy types have different strengths and weaknesses. Vary your loadout to best deal with each.
  - If you don't think you can win a fight, don't take it.

  When you arrive on-site, you'll be told which direction the objective is in.
  There'll be a building in that direction; break in and complete your objective.
  Note: North is towards the top of the screen in default rotation (default keybinding: [color=#028ed9][keybind="CameraReset"/][/color]).

  While planetside you will be unable to communicate via radio with the wider Frontier Sector, and unless you have a [color=#a4885c]telecommunication server[/color] installed you won't be able to use radio to communicate with your crew in the expedition either.

  # Being prepared
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobBloodCultistZealotMelee"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobFleshGolemExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobArgocyteEnforcerExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobCarpHoloExpeditions"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobRogueSiliconHunter"/>
  </Box>
  During missions planetside, you will encounter dangers ranging from inhospitable environments to hostile wildlife and even blood-thirsty cultists or relentless automatons. If you want to survive and get off the planet richer than you were before you got to be prepared for the challenges ahead. You will need the right gear and the knowledge of how and when that gear should be used. And most importantly you will need the help of your crewmates.

  # Gear
  ## Environmental hazards
  The first thing you will encounter on the planet is The Planet itself. Environmental conditions on planets are diverse: not every planet has a breathable atmosphere or atmosphere at all and temperatures fluctuate significantly. The [color=#a4885c]salvage console[/color] will give you a rough idea of what conditions on the planet are in the [color=#a4885c]Modifiers[/color] section of the mission description. This information will help you to decide what environmental protection gear you need if you need any at all.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FloorLiquidPlasmaEntity"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FloorLavaEntity"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Biomes:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Grassland/Caves/Shadow:[/bold] no hazards have been observed so far.
  - [bold]Snow:[/bold] liquid plasma pools can be encountered in this biome. Touching one will result in setting self on fire.
  - [bold]Lava:[/bold] lava pools can be encountered in this biome. Touching one will result in setting self on fire.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingMaskGas"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirTankFilled"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Air quality modifiers:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]None:[/bold] the air is safe to breathe without internals on.
  - [bold]Dangerous atmosphere:[/bold] ranges from the toxic atmosphere to complete lack of it, requires internals toggled on at the very least and wearing sealed EVA or hardsuit in extreme cases.
  - [bold]Volatile atmosphere:[/bold] the atmosphere contains gaseous plasma in it. Requires internals on. Depending on what other gases are present, there is a distinct possibility of starting a plasma fire that will eventually engulf the entire planet.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterWinterMiner"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitEVA"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterHardsuitBasic"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Temperature modifiers:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]None:[/bold] the temperatures on the planet are comfortable and no special equipment is needed.
  - [bold]Low temperature:[/bold] cold, but bearable unless you are a lizard (in that case wearing a winter coat or a hardsuit is advisable).
  - [bold]Extreme cold:[/bold] temperatures are close to absolute zero, so a hardsuit is required.
  - [bold]High temperature:[/bold] unpleasantly hot. 150 centigrade hot. Heat-resistant gear or a hardsuit is required.
  - [bold]Extreme heat:[/bold] temperatures are so high that wearing a hardsuit is mandatory.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Flare"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GlowstickBlue"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FlashlightLantern"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Floodlight"/>
  </Box>
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Time of day:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Morning/Day/Evening times:[/bold] the ambient light on the planet is sufficient, no need for light sources.
  - [bold]Night time:[/bold] pitch black darkness, light sources are required for navigating the planet.
  
  [bold][color=#a4885c]Time constraints:[/color][/bold]
  - [bold]Rush:[/bold] you will have less time to complete the expedition. Set your priorities in advance and try to avoid wearing too much gear with negative speed modifiers.
  
  ## Tools
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Pickaxe"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Crowbar"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wrench"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Screwdriver"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wirecutter"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesGlassesMeson"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Welder"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Multitool"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RadioHandheld"/>
  </Box>
  Salvaging often requires digging through layers of rocks to reach an abandoned facility, as well as deconstructing various obstacles, such as walls and windows, to gain entrance to the ruins. This may also involve prying open unpowered airlocks or dismantling valuable machinery to facilitate transportation. The tools you possess can either make tasks easier, such as using a crowbar to pry open airlocks, which is significantly faster than doing so by hand, or even make certain tasks possible in the first place, like requiring a mining tool to dig through rocks. Additionally, tools can provide a means of communication between crewmates when a telecommunication server is unavailable, such as using a handheld radios.
  
  For more details see guidebook entries on [textlink="engineering" link="Engineering"] and [textlink="construction" link="Construction"].
  
  ## Medicine
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EmergencyMedipen"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Brutepack"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Ointment"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gauze"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicatedSuture"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RegenerativeMesh"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Tourniquet"/>
  </Box>
  You are going to get hurt. Period. Knowing the basics of medical care and having some medical supplies close at hand in time of need is the difference between life and death for you or your fellow crewmates. 
  
  Before embarking on an expedition consider stocking some medical supplies for the common damage types you are likely to receive ([color=red]brute[/color] and [color=#ffa500]burn[/color]) as well as tools for stopping [color=red]bleeding[/color], like [color=#a4885c]gauze[/color] or [color=#a4885c]emergency medipen[/color]. The most basic medications can be procured from vending machines, however, the advanced and more efficient ones are harder to obtain, but most of the time they can be bought from other players, providing medical services.
  
  Having medical tools at hand is half of the job: before going on an adventure be sure to learn the basics of medical care.
  
  For more details see guidebook entry on [textlink="medical" link="Medical Doctor"].
  
  ## Armor
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadHelmetBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterArmorBulletproof"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterArmorReflective"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RiotShield"/>
  </Box>
  Most of the time, you won't be able to avoid getting hit. Wearing armor will reduce the impact of damage on your health, allowing you to remain in action for a longer period and potentially giving you enough time to administer medicine. Since hostile entities in abandoned facilities inflict various types of damage, choosing your armor wisely will significantly increase your chances of survival.
  
  Here are some examples for your consideration:
  - [color=#a4885c]Syndicate naval forces[/color] use firearms that deal [color=yellow]piercing[/color] type of damage: wearing armor with high protection against this type of damage (like a bulletproof vest) will significantly reduce the damage you take;
  - [color=#a4885c]Rogue silicones[/color] primarily deal [color=#ffa500]heat[/color] type of damage: wearing a reflective vest is a good choice when facing rogue silicons.
  
  ## Teamwork
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcGood"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcBad"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcUgly"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GuidebookMemeNpcThatGuy"/>
  </Box>
  By far, your best bet at surviving expeditions is your crewmates.  You might [italic]know[/italic] how to heal yourself, but you [italic]can't[/italic] if you're unconscious.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TelecomServerFilledShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EncryptionKeyCommon"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadsetGrey" Caption="headset"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EncryptionKeyMedical"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MedicalTrackingImplanter"/>
  </Box>
  
  Communication is crucial. Make sure to keep your teammates informed about your status and inquire about their well-being. To maintain contact with your crew, you need either a functioning [color=#a4885c]telecommunication server[/color] with [color=#a4885c]encryption keys[/color] installed, or distribute [color=#a4885c]handheld radios[/color] among crew members (and ensure they are turned on).

  Additionally, having [color=#a4885c]medical encryption keys[/color] installed in your and your crew's headsets, as well as [color=#a4885c]medical tracking implanters[/color] applied, will enable instant notification if one of you goes down in combat.
  
  ## Know your enemy
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesHudMedical"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingEyesHudDiagnostic"/>
  </Box>
  Adaptability is key: strategies and tactics that work against [color=#a4885c]Xenos[/color] might not work well against [color=#a4885c]mercenaries[/color], and vice versa. The Guidebook entries on hostile entities may provide some insight into what to expect planetside, but they [italic]cannot[/italic] replace firsthand experience. Instead, descend to the planet, salvage what you can, and face danger head-on. The riches won't wait around forever!
  
</Document>