<Document>
  # Piloting
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerShuttle"/>
  </Box>
  To move a shuttle, you first need to click on the [color=#a4885c]shuttle console[/color] in its cockpit. After clicking the shuttle console, you should see a radar view of the space around your shuttle.

Newly purchased shuttles start docked with Frontier Outpost. To undock, follow these steps:

- Tell people you are undocking using the traffic radio channel ([color=#CC6633]:d[/color]). Include your ship's callsign, which can be found on the NAV screen (e.g. "[color=#CC6633]:d Pioneer NX-123 undocking.[/color]")
- Click on the DOCK tab, disconnect any airlocks that are docked to the station.
- Return to the NAV tab.

- To move a shuttle, the default controls (for a QWERTY keyboard) are:

-[color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleStrafeUp"/][/color] & [color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleStrafeDown"/][/color]: Move forward and backward.
-[color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleStrafeLeft"/][/color] & [color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleStrafeRight"/][/color]: Move left and right.
-[color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleRotateLeft"/][/color] & [color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleRotateRight"/][/color]: Rotate left and right.
-[color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleBrake"/][/color]: Slow down.
-[color=#028ed9][keybind="ShuttleBrake"/][/color] + [color=#028ed9]any input[/color]: Move and rotate slowly.

# Docking
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirlockGlassShuttle"/>
  </Box>
  [bold]Before docking your ship with:[/bold]
- [bold][color=#979797]Another ship[/color][/bold], it is best practice to announce your intention to dock over the traffic channel ([color=#CC6633]:d[/color]).
- [bold][color=#ffd700]Frontier Outpost[/color][/bold], stop 200m out, request permission to dock from the Station Traffic Controller (STC) over the traffic radio channel ([color=#CC6633]:d[/color]).
- [bold][color=#ffa500]Another station[/color][/bold], docks are first come, first serve. Be courteous and leave space where possible.

To dock the ship:
- Pilot towards the target so a set of its airlocks are nearby a set of airlocks of the target.
- When very close, click on the DOCK tab for a closer view.
- When next to the airlock, you can click "Dock" when highlighted to attach to the target.
</Document>