<Document>
  # New Frontiers Shipyards

To assist in developing the Frontier, shuttles from Nanotrasen and its subsidiaries can be rented for use.
All rentals last for one shift. Rented shuttles return to Nanotrasen at the end of shift.
The value of shuttles is returned to the purchaser when ended through a ship console.
To avoid losses, [bold]make sure you end your rental before ending your shift[/bold].

## Shipyard Console
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PassengerIDCard"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SpaceCash1000"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerShipyard"/>
  </Box>
  To rent a ship:
- Eject the ID card from your PDA.
- Insert the ID card into an unused [color=#cccc00]shipyard console[/color].
- Use the shipyard console to bring up its interface.
- Select the ship you would like to rent.
- Press the Purchase button on the console.
- Press the Eject button to remove your ID from the console.
- Reinsert your ID card into your PDA.

Congratulations, you're now the Captain of your own ship!

To end your rental:
- Make sure your rented ship is docked with Frontier Outpost.
- Make sure nobody is aboard the ship.
- Eject the ID card [bold]used to purchase the ship[/bold] from your PDA.
- Insert the ID card into an unused [color=#cccc00]shipyard console[/color].
- Use the shipyard console to bring up its interface.
- Press the Sell button on the console. The value will be deposited into your bank account.
- Press the Eject button to remove your ID from the console.
- Reinsert your ID card into your PDA.

## Provisions
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="LockerCaptain"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SuitStorageBase"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="LockerParamedic"/>
  </Box>
  Ships come equipped with the tools and supplies needed to perform one or more tasks in the Frontier (e.g. mining, research, medical, food services).

Ships, especially larger ones, work best with a crew. Refer to the [bold]Hiring[/bold] section for more info.
Space is a lonely, dangerous place, and you'll have a much better time when you work with a crew.

</Document>
