The Station Rep keeps things moving on the Frontier Outpost. They provide a number of important functions to the sector, like paying employees, helping people with ship registration, and representing NT interests throughout the sector.

This guide is mostly intended for people who either are already whitelisted, or are actively pursuing a whitelist. It assumes that you have interacted with an SR before and generally know how the game works, and just need help with the details.

# SR Basics 
You have four machines available to you as SR to do your job: The ID Card Computer, the Shuttle Record Computer, the Station Records Computer, and Station Administration. You also have a vending machine which contains a bunch of paperwork templates, as well as fresh PDAs and IDs.

The first thing to do is find your SR folder. It's a green folder, and there should be one in your office. You can buy extras from your vending machine. It contains all the paperwork you're likely to need. Every time you need a piece of paperwork, ''put the paperwork in your fax machine and copy it'' before using your copy. Always, always, always keep your original copy in the folder.

## ID Card Computer
The ID Card Computer is used to change ship titles, job titles, and ID card permissions.

To use it, first put your ID card into it, and then put in the ID card to be edited. "Privileged ID" should be your ID, "Target ID" should be the one that you're editing. 

You can change the name, title, and shuttle name attached to the target ID here. Just put in the changed text and click Save. When changing titles and shuttle names, be sure to check what the requested title/name is, and that it isn't obscene or disruptive. A merc asking for their ship to be named "NFSD" and their title to be "Bailiff" probably doesn't have the sector's best interests at heart.

You can also change permissions attached to the ID. Adding the Captain permission is pretty safe, that goes to anyone who buys a ship automatically, and really anyone can have it. All the others should be added only when needed. You can also use the preset dropdown to give someone the same job permissions as someone of the selected job. For example, if a mail carrier loses their PDA, you can buy them a new ID card and give it the Mail Carrier preset.

If someone wants a ship rename or a title change, give them a copy of the shuttle name change form and ask them to fill it out and hand you their ID so you can make the change. Be sure to stamp the form, give a copy to the requester, and keep one on file.

## Shuttle Records Computer 
The main use for the Shuttle Records Computer is to retitle salvaged ships. If someone has legitimately gone through the 20-minute salvage process, you can use the Shuttle Records Computer to give them ownership of the ship they have salvaged.

Use your best judgement on whether the salvage process was done properly. Ideally, they reach out to you at the start of the process and you can watch them do the whole process, but if that doesn't happen then judgement comes into play. You should generally err on the side of not retitling a ship if there's genuine ambiguity. Remember, if you retitle a ship you're giving someone's ship to someone else. If you're confident that the ship is truly abandoned, then there's no harm. But if not, someone is getting their ship stolen with your help.

There is no paperwork template for retitling a ship, but many SRs will make ad-hoc paperwork to describe who is asking for the retitle, who previously owned the ship, and if a fee was collected.

Take the ID of the requester and insert it into the computer. Look up the ship to be retitled, and check the cost. This cost is taken from the station funds. You are allowed, but not required, to ask for this money as a fee for executing the transfer. Just click Copy Deed to ID Card and the ship will be retitled to the new owner. Hand back the ID and you're done!

You can also use this computer to check the details of who owns what ship, which is occasionally useful to the NFSD.

## Station Records Computer 
This works just like the shuttle records computer in a normal shuttle. The main use of this computer is to add role slots that you need to fill for station employees. If you want to have a second SR come help you out, this is where you'd open their slot. Same if you need to hire extra Mail Carriers or Security Guards.

This computer is pretty self-explanatory, you can search for a person based on their name or job with the dropdown at the top, or open slots for people using the plus and minus buttons next to that role on the bottom left. Just like a normal records computer, the only people who are tracked in the list are ones who spawned on this station, so people who spawned on the MD, PP, EL, or NFSDO won't appear in the list.

## Station Administration
This is your station bank account. You are generally allowed to use it as you see fit, as long as you do so reasonably. The definition of "reasonable" is intentionally vauge, but part of getting whitelisted is the admins and community in general trusting your judgement and roleplay sense. So trust yourself; if you think an expense is reasonable, it probably is.

To withdraw, put an amount to withdraw, pick the reason closest to what you're withdrawing it for, give a short description of what you're getting it for, and click Withdraw. The admins will check these sometimes, but as long as you're doing something reasonable there won't be an issue. Taking 10,000 spesos for "Buying food" is fine, taking 1,000,000 spesos for "funny clown show" probably isn't. 

To deposit, insert spesos just like you would for an ATM, and fill out the deposit fields just like you would the withdrawal fields.

## Other Resources 
You have a uniform printer in your office, as well as some cloth and durathread to use it. You can use this as you see fit: Make yourself some drip, make a new uniform for your employees, make carpet, or whatever you'd like. Remember that other SRs are likely to come on after you, though, so don't use it all up for yourself without restocking it somehow. Like most resources you have access to, the key is to be thoughtful and reasonable with your actions.

You have a filing cabinet. This is where you should generally put your paperwork, for organization.

You have a gun safe. This has a gun, as well as 2 CDET turrets. CDET turrets are nonlethal turrets that shoot anyone wearing contraband. Possession of contraband is against server rules on the FO, so someone being shot by one of these should generally be ahelped, and/or told to leave their contra on their ship. To use one, pick it up (it takes two hands), stand where you want it to be, and click yourself. There will be a progress meter, and the CDET will be placed.

You have a locker. This locker has a spare SR ID, as well as a few other critical pieces of equipment. Keep this locked at all times. Allowing someone to take your ID is a serious issue, and everything else in here is almost as problematic to let out.

In the STC office, there is an Announcement Computer. Use this to send messages to the whole server at once. Typically this is used for reminders, like requests to turn on suit coords, requests for server-wide aid, or declaring an NFZ if there is no Sheriff on.


# SR Duties 
While that covers the basics of how to perform the job of SR, it doesn't really get into what your general priorities are.

In short, the SR has tremendous trust placed in them by the admins and community at large to help make an interesting and positive roleplay experience for everybody. If what you're doing can be reasonably expected to make the game experience more fun, you can probably do it.

## Staff Pay 
One of your most important duties is making sure everyone gets paid. You are required by server rules to make sure all the FO staff is able to be paid. Minimum wage is 20k per hour for yourself and the Sheriff, 15k for all other security personnel (including the Guard), and 10k for everyone else. Most SRs pay more than minimum wage, and additionally give bonuses for good work. Giving bonuses to the Mail Carrier based on successfully delivering mail (which puts money into the FO account) is common as well. Every SR does things differently, though. If you want to be generous but demanding, or stingy but lax, that's your prerogative. The one big thing to keep in mind is to not give out ridiculous bonuses; don't just cash out the whole balance of the account at the end of the shift to give everyone huge bonuses.

If one of the other stations needs some cash to pay payroll, you may be asked to lend them money. Maybe the NFSD lost its money buying ships that got blown up by pirates and they can't pay out combat pay. Maybe the PM singloosed and doesn't have access to their account to pay the plant techs. There are many possibilities where your account is the only one with money in it. In this case, you need to make sure that everyone makes at least minimum wage if at all possible. You don't need to pay any more than that, though if you have the funds then paying a more fair wage is a good thing. You also have the ability to fly to the NFSDO, MD, or PP and access the station account yourself to pay out of those, if you're just missing a commander.

## Projects 
If you're confident that you've got staff pay squared away, the rest of your budget can be spent on projects. This has incredible leeway in what you're allowed to do, as long as you stick to the principle that the FO account is primarily there to encourage interesting RP.

Most SRs will, at minimum, contact a food ship and make a food order to keep the FO staff fed. This food can be put in the fridge in the break room on the southeast corner of the station.

SRs can also hire people to renovate or improve the FO, subject to normal server rules. You can't install a science lab, but you can set up a petting zoo, or commission a mural. You can do the same for any other station. For example, if you'd like to hire a bartender or chef to keep Tinnia's operating, or a dealer to run the Casino, you can do that.

Another common project is a loan or grant given to a new player who is short on funds. If a new player loses their first ship, they might not have enough raw money to buy another, and a 15k loan can get them back on their feet. You can generally give people money for any reasonable purpose, as long as you think the money requested is reasonable and you think offering the loan/grant will improve RP overall.

You can even get things for yourself, if it could make a cool story. Offering a bounty on cats and cognizine can be fun, or asking for a specific musical instrument to be delivered to you.

# Going Out 
While your main office is on the FO and you should probably spend most of your time there until you get comfortable, you are fully allowed to leave if you'd like. You even have a ship purpose-built for this, the Duchess. The Duchess has all four of your normal machines on it, and lets you have a mobile SR office wherever you go. If you want to operate from a dock in the Trade Mall, or even just going where you're needed, that's fine. You can also combine with with projects; maybe you can fund a cooking competition at Tinnia's that you judge for? Remember that leaving FO opens you up to piracy, which is both a risk and a fun opportunity.

# Law Enforcement 
The most important thing to remember about law enforcement as an SR is that ''law enforcement is not your job!'' You have some privileges that you may exercise at your discretion if you think that would make the overall RP experience of the server better, but if a law break happens anywhere other than the FO, you are ''not obligated'' to help out yourself, aside from reporting the crime to your Guard and/or the NFSD. Generally speaking, you should cooperate with the NFSD and help them how you can, but leave actual law enforcement to the law.

Broadly speaking, you have the authority to do anything a Sheriff can (outside of hiring Cadets) if there's no Sheriff around to do it instead. You can sign contra permits, do contra buybacks, process warrants, negotiate with pirates, or anything else that generally needs a Sheriff to do. However, ''you are not the Sheriff'', and you are never ''required'' to take on Sheriff responsibilities outside of making sure NFSD officers get paid. Additionally, as you are not in the NFSD command chain, you do not have formal authority to order officers around. You can certainly ''ask'' them to do things, but just as you are not required to perform NFSD-related duties, they are not required to listen to your orders.

Basically, you're there so if there's paperwork that needs to be signed, you can sign it. If a sergeant needs a warrant signed to execute a search or a medic needs permission to enter a UIV and you're convinced that the request is good, you should sign it to help enable other people's RP.  And if someone needs to be a leader in extremis, you can do that. But you shouldn't generally be exposing yourself to danger if you can help it, and you should leave the actual enforcement of laws to the people who chose a law enforcement role when they logged in, rather than stepping on their toes.

The one place where you really should be enforcing the law is the FO. Breaking the law on the FO is against server rules, so generally if you see someone breaking a law there, ahelp it, and then talk to them to find out what exactly they're doing and contact in-game law enforcement as appropriate. If someone really is just confused and doesn't understand the zero-tolerance rule but isn't malicious, the admins will see that and nothing bad will happen. But telling admins regardless of the severity of the crime is the right move, as they can track if there's long-term problems with a particular player and react accordingly.

# Closing 
If you're ever unsure about where the line is between what you ''can'' do and what you ''should'' do, send an ahelp and ask an admin. Tell them what you're thinking of doing or not doing, and get their input. They always welcome being given a heads up when something borderline or weird is going on.
