The [color=DarkOrange]Station Traffic Controller[/color] has a very important job that can make or break a shift for a lot of people. A good [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] is the difference between being able to [color=Lime]sell your cargo easily[/color] and a [color=Red]gunfight breaking out over docking ports[/color]. 

Like all command, the [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] is a whitelist role, and so you're expected to know how the game works, but this guidebook entry will describe how to be an STC in a way that is fun, effective, and promotes interesting roleplay, without needing any deep knowledge on anything else.


# Your Job 

The basics of the [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] job are outlined in the Server Rules and [color=OliveDrab]Space Law[/color]. 

Your job is to keep traffic through the [color=Blue]Frontier Outpost[/color] and [color=Cornsilk]Trade Mall[/color] free-flowing, and make sure no one is stuck without being able to dock for long. 

The [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] is primarily a roleplaying role, with most of what you do involving talking to people, [color=Chartreuse]de-escalating conflict[/color], and keeping things in motion. Though occasionally, it involves getting in your powerhouse of a ship -The Harbormaster- and enforcing [color=OliveDrab]docking law[/color] manually.

## The Rules

In general, you need to make sure that people don't dock for too long, and use good roleplaying and enforcement discretion to keep ships moving. 

[color=Teal]You don't want to be too strict[/color], since this is a game and not a second job, but be too forgiving and people won't have a place to sell their cargo.

*Ships may only dock for up to 10 minutes. On the Frontier Outpost, docking extensions '''cannot''' be granted, except for station staff. On Trade, extensions can be granted at your (or the SR's) discretion.  

* If someone is docked over 10 minutes, and does not immediately leave when notified, you have the right to forcibly eject them from the station, or [color=Red]fine[/color] them at your discretion.

* Staff's privilege of extended docking at the station is only at your (or the SR's) discretion. If a staff member is tying up a dock for a long time, you can ask that they sell their ship, or move it somewhere away from a dock. You are the authority on parking over everyone else, just remember that RP comes first over perfect parking enforcement.

* Service ships are not allowed to operate on the Frontier Outpost. Generally keeping ships to a 10-minute docking time will make this not an issue, but it's good to know that on the Frontier Outpost in particular.

food ships are not allowed to sell food, med ships are not allowed to sell chems, and in general service ships of any kind aren't allowed to be open for business until they leave the station. Even the SR can't override this.

** That said, service ships '''are''' allowed to operate on Trade. If a ship isn't causing a traffic issue, you are well within your rights to allow them to continue to operate past the normal time limit. The SR can issue a waiver to allow this formally, and if there is no SR, you can do the same as STC. Generally, if you want to issue a docking waiver, the SR will let you, just check with them first.

* You cannot charge people for docking in any case. You can fine people for overstay, but you can't require "docking fees" for normal dock usage.

* Space Law does not specifically limit your authority to FO and Trade, although the vast majority of the time, that's where you'll be enforcing parking restrictions. 

If there's a parking issue at another station and you are ordered to help out by the SR, the law is ambiguous enough to allow that.

** One way to look at this: You '''must''' enforce docking law on the Frontier Outpost. You '''can''' enforce docking law on Trade, if you feel it is needed. You '''may''' enforce docking law elsewhere, if asked to.

[color=OliveDrab]Space Law[/color] describes a process to request and grant docking permission. 

While it's good to encourage people to announce when they're docking, in practice people requesting and being granted docking permission slows down the docking process and results in traffic that doesn't flow as well. 

However, many people find that the call-and-response of this process is very satisfying from a roleplay perspective. Additionally, some people feel strongly that keeping specific docks clear (like the dock closest to the mail area) has a positive effect on the round, and use this docking procedure to enforce that. 

You have discretion over how exactly to do your job as [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] (just like every job on the Frontier), and how strictly to adhere to this docking procedure is part of that.

The docking procedure is as follows:

1. The ship seeking to dock uses the [color=DarkOrange]Traffic Comms[/color] (either using the intercom in their ship console (or the :d channel on the chat window) to announce their ship designation and intended docking location.

* Ideally they give the full designation including ship name and random ID, but as long as you can unambiguously identify the ship, it's acceptable.

* Ideally they tell you the specific dock they want to dock to. This is especially important at Trade, where you need to know whether they're using a cargo dock or a normal one. Feel free to ask if it's relevant. And always feel free to override a requested dock if you want to put them somewhere else.

* According to the text of Space Law, they're supposed to tell you why they're docking, like "selling cargo" or "selling the ship to cryo" or "picking up crew". Very few people do this, and it's really only relevant if someone is selling their items/cargo.

2. In response, you tell them whether or not they can dock, and what dock to go to.

* In the vast, vast majority of situations, you will not be refusing docking permission. Really the only time when that might happen is if there literally isn't space for them. In that case, you might tell them what dock you think will free up for them soon, so they can be ready to park there.

* You have final authority on where people park. Someone parking somewhere other than where you tell them is generally not enough of a problem to levy a fine, but it's certainly reason to send them an annoyed holocall if it's a big deal.

3. When the pilot is undocking, they again call out their ship ID and intention to undock.

4. You respond to them granting permission to undock once it's safe to do so.

* Again, in the overwhelming majority of cases you'll just grant permission. The only time you wouldn't is if you see a ship that might crash into the one asking to leave. In a case like that, you'd want to ask them to wait a minute before leaving.

Many STCs who use this docking procedure will simply accept any request to dock or undock, just watching chat and immediately responding when asked. If you find yourself doing this, maybe ask yourself if adhering to this process is helpful and RP-enhancing, or if you want to focus on other things.

# Your Tools 

## The FO and Trade Consoles 

On the left side of the [color=DarkOrange]STC's[/color] desk in their office/the Harbormaster are two consoles that effectively act as ship piloting consoles for the FO/Trade. 

You can't move the stations, but you ''can'' use the normal dock UI to forcibly undock ships. 

The main use for these consoles is to keep an eye on who is currently docked, and when you need to eject someone, to allow you to undock them.

## The STC Folder 

You spawn with a folder full of paperwork forms. 

Keep this folder on you '''at all times'''. When you need to use one of the documents in it, put that document in a fax machine and select Copy in the fax menu, then Eject in the right-click menu to get the original back out. 

Keep the blank version in the folder while you're using an active copy.

The most important form here is the Hourly Traffic Log, Every time a ship docks or undocks, note the ship and the time, Compare that time to the current shift time. When the ship undocks, note that it has undocked. 

You can note the time of undock if you'd like, but that's not usually an important piece of information, so only do that if you feel it enhances your RP.

At the end of the hour, sign the log, stamp it, and put it away. 
Keep it in your folder if there's space, give it to the SR to file in their cabinet, wherever you'd like to put it. 

It probably won't be relevant later, but having a bunch of signed and stamped traffic logs is another one of those RP-enhancing things that you can choose to do. If you'd rather just dump it in the trash when you're done with it, that is allowed.

The other forms are pretty self-explanatory. Take some time to read over them, but they're much more rarely used than the Traffic Log.

## Your Ship, the Harbormaster 

The [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] spawns with a voucher for a ship called [color=FireBrick]The Harbormaster[/color]. [color=FireBrick]The Harbormaster[/color] is one of your most powerful tools. It's basically a tugboat; it has many engines in each direction and can accelerate better than basically any other ship. 

It's got enough [color=Red]power[/color] to stop anything in its tracks. It can accelerate to max speed while in Park. It can drag a Crescent away from a station with ease. Additionally, it has the same FO/Trade consoles that are in the normal [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] office.

Use your [color=Green]voucher[/color] to get one of these at the start of your shift, and keep it with you forever. 

The normal [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] office can be useful if you want to spend time near the [color=Lime]SR[/color], but [color=FireBrick]The Harbormaster[/color] is your most powerful tool for parking enforcement, and you'll generally be more effective the more time you spend in it.

just be sure to remember to [color=FireBrick]turn off the generator[/color] when it's parked.

# The Process 

The [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] job can be [color=FireBrick]stressful[/color] at times, This process describes a way to do the job that is engaging and encourages good RP both for [color=LawnGreen]yourself and other people[/color] in the sector. 

But it's important to emphasize: This is just one way to do the job. As long as you're doing your best to [color=LawnGreen]keep traffic flowing and enforcing the 10 minute docking timer[/color] in one way or another, you'll do fine. 

There are as many ways to be an STC as there are STC players, so don't worry about dogmatically following anything outside of the basic server rules on docking.

In general, this process is very simple.

1. Use your [color=FireBrick]Harbormaster[/color] voucher, pick up a couple extra Bananium fuel cells. Get in [color=FireBrick]The Harbormaster[/color], don't leave unless you have to.

2. Keep track of docking times at FO and Trade as best you can.

3. If it looks like someone might overstay, warn them. If someone ''does'' overstay, go to their ship in person and ask them to move quickly.

4. If the ship is [color=DimGray]abandoned[/color], or the pilot [color=Red]refuses to move quickly[/color], undock them using the FO/Trade consoles, and use the Harbormaster to gently move them away from the station. Once you can access their dock, dock using the Harbormaster and drag them to 400m from the station.

And that's basically it! 90% of the time, when told in person that they're violating docking procedure people will be contrite and actually move. 

That's good behavior to reward, and it's generally better to err on the side of mercy. That last 10% of the time, they might ignore you, [color=DarkRed]they might yell at you, they might give you bad excuses[/color]. [color=LawnGreen]RP with them[/color] -They might be doing it to cause conflict for the sake of a story- and follow good escalation,  but once you've told them that they're in violation and they refuse to move quickly, you have the right and the ship to move them yourself.

Some tips on this process that might be helpful:

* If you notice on your form that a ship has been docked over 5 minutes, send a reminder that there's a 10 minute docking limit. 

You can use the Traffic or Common channel for this, or even holocall the ship. At about 8 minutes, make a trip in person if you can. Make every effort to contact them before they hit the 10 minute limit.

* If an overstaying ship is dead (ie. has no power, otherwise seems abandoned) then check it for SSD players. 

Pull any SSD players out to the station. Give the same warnings you normally do, but don't wait more than a few seconds for a response before you move the ship out.

* Remember that ship collision damage is a thing, and keep under 10 m/s when nudging a ship. 

Also know that your handling will be terrible when dragging a docked ship. You just need to get used to it. 

Be very careful when towing, since you'll have a much harder time braking than usual. You don't want to hit someone who is flying by.

* You could get yelled at! You could get shot! People in general don't like it when the rules are applied to them, and if someone is ignoring you, they aren't going to be happy when you don't let them ignore you anymore. 

Remember the escalation rules, and ahelp if someone boards your ship and shoots you without a word. There's all sorts of things to do for personal defense, but remember that turning yourself into a walking armory just in case someone is a dick would be frowned on. Better to get shot and ahelp it (and hopefully get healed up later) than break escalation yourself. Remember that you're not an [color=OliveDrab]NFSD officer[/color], you're a [color=DarkOrange]civilian traffic official[/color].

# Your Best Friend: The Security Guard 

Having a [color=LightCoral]Security Guard[/color] friend isn't assured, but when you have one, it makes the in-person part of the job safer, and gives you more enforcement tools. 

It also lets you effectively be in two places at once. The most common infraction to happen on the FO or Trade is dock overstay, so generally you should expect to take up a lot of the [color=IndianRed]Guard's[/color] time.

## Fines 

[color=Red]Fines[/color] are pretty hard to enforce alone. If someone doesn't want to pay, [color=Red]they can just ignore you[/color]. You can report them to the NFSD, but generally they have better things to do than chase down docking fines.

However, if you have a [color=IndianRed]Guard[/color], then enforcing fines becomes much more possible. You have a [color=Sienna]Docking Violation fine document[/color] in your [color=DarkOrange]STC[/color] folder. If you feel that a fine is necessary, fill that out, sign it, send it to the [color=LawnGreen]SR[/color] to be signed and stamped if you have one, then give the form to [color=IndianRed]The Guard[/color] to issue. [color=IndianRed]The Guard[/color], being someone with a gun and handcuffs, is much more likely to get a real response from an obstinate parker than you will as a civilian.

[color=Red]The maximum fine[/color] for docking is 10,000 spesos for each 10 minutes past the first. It's up to you to decide how much to charge. However, keep in mind that the annoyance of having to pay ''at all'' is a big part of the punishment, and even a very long dock overstay isn't likely to put a dent on an experienced player's shift. There's nothing wrong with being [color=LimeGreen]merciful[/color].

That said, if they're being a dick about it, throw the book at them.

Once you've collected a [color=Red]fine[/color], bring it to the [color=Lime]SR[/color] to be deposited in the station budget. If you don't have an [color=Lime]SR[/color], keep the fines in your office/Harbormaster. When you cryo, if there still isn't an [color=Lime]SR[/color], go to the Mail vendor near the mail room and get some packaging paper. Put the fines in a package, label it "fines", and leave it on your desk in the FO office. The [color=Lime]SR[/color] can deposit them when they log in.

Remember than money you collect in fines [color=Red]is not yours[/color], it is station property. Embezzling fines is a great way to get an STC/Guard roleban.

## Wellness Checks 

One of the most common reasons for overstay is someone simply [color=RoyalBlue]cryoing and forgetting to sell their ship[/color]. Manually checking every ship can be time-consuming, and in [color=OrangeRed]high-traffic times[/color] it can be tough to keep up with dockings when trying to discern the status of overstaying ships.

[color=IndianRed]The Guard[/color] can help here by doing more regular wellness checks on docked ships. [color=IndianRed]A guard[/color] simply poking their head in can find out what's going on, and communicate the 10 minute docking timer. While they do this, you can be keeping track of further dockings, or even doing your own wellness checks on the other station.

## Belligerent Offenders 

If someone is very clearly hostile towards you when you try to enforce docking times, your first call should be to [color=IndianRed]the Guard[/color]. Their job is to [color=Red]enforce station law[/color], and often they have the tools to de-escalate what could be a violent encounter.

[color=OliveDrab]The NFSD[/color] can also help here, but again, they often have something more important to do. If someone [color=Red]actually fires shots[/color] at either yourself or the Guard, definitely involve them, though, as assault is a much more serious offense than a docking overstay.
[color=OliveDrab][/color]
