<Document>
# Gas Mining
Asteroids in the Frontier sector are a reliable source of large amounts of normally gaseous elements in the form of [color=gold]solidified deposits[/color].

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasDepositOxygen" Caption="oxygen deposit"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasDepositNitrogen" Caption="nitrogen deposit"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasDepositPlasma" Caption="plasma deposit"/>
</Box>

Atmospheric ships, for example, the [color=yellow]Gasbender[/color] and [color=yellow]Ambition[/color], come equipped with the equipment needed to extract from these deposits. Check for the [color=cyan]Atmospherics[/color] category at the [color=steelblue]shipyard console[/color] when buying ships.

## Needed Equipment

The equipment you'll need:
- A mining drill
- A portable gaslock
- Steel for pipes
- A source of power (J.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. recommended)
- LV cable
- A gas deposit locator (optional)

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMiningDrill"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GaslockFrame"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorJrPacman" Caption="power supply"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasDepositLocator"/>
</Box>

## Mining Procedure

Standard procedure for drilling for gas is as follows:

1. Find an asteroid with gas deposits on it. A [color=green]gas deposit scanner[/color] can help you find these, it'll beep when it's close to one, print one off at an [color=orange]engineering techfab[/color].

2. Drill out some of the asteroid, and look for [color=lightpink]whisps of solid elements[/color].

3. Anchor your gas mining drill onto the deposit.

4. Build a set of pipes connecting the drill to the most convenient edge of the asteroid.

5. Make sure that your shuttle can dock with the edge. You may find constructing a lattice jetty can help.

6. Note that gas filters, mixers and other equipment may not work on the asteroid. For efficient processing, set up your shuttle for onboard filtration, processing and storage.

7. Anchor a portable gaslock onto the edge of the asteroid. Point the red outlet port with the docking lights out towards space.

8. Dock your shuttle's gaslock with the portable gaslock, do this with the shuttle console like you're docking with a station.

9. Anchor a portable generator on the asteroid, turn it on, and set up cables so both the mining drill and portable gaslock are powered.

10. Set the target pressure on your drill.

11. Set the pressure and direction on both the portable gaslock and your shuttle's gaslock.

12. Note that the gaslocks are bidirectional, and the direction the lights are moving is the direction the gas will flow. Both should point in the same direction to pump gas.

13. Wait until the gas deposit is depleted - the light on the miner should glow [color=yellow]yellow[/color] when low, and [color=red]red[/color] when empty. If you find other deposits, it is efficient to pump multiple deposits at the same time!

14. If the miner glows [color=orange]orange[/color], your pipe network is backed up. Double check your pressures and pump directions!

## Gas Filtering and Processing

Gas deposits are impure, and should be filtered before selling. [color=cyan]Gas filters[/color] can help extract one gas at a time through their side port.

Different gases have different values. The most valuable gases are [color=cyan]frezon[/color] followed by [color=limegreen]tritium[/color]. Ask someone who knows more about atmospherics about how to process plasma into tritium, and tritium into frezon.

Selling gas can be done through canisters, which can be crafted from [color=gray]plasteel[/color], or in bulk at a [color=lightgreen]gas sale point[/color], e.g. at Edison Power Plant.

- Canisters can be sold using cargo pallets and cargo sales consoles, like any other good.
- Gas sales points can accept massive amounts of gas at a time, and require gas to be pumped in through a gaslock.

Both sales methods pay according to the [bold]purity[/bold] of your mix. Be sure to filter your gas! The easier it is for NT to separate your gases out, the better the pay.

Best of luck out there, greenhorn, and keep at it.

</Document>
