<Document>
# 5. General Roleplay Guidelines

Your IC name must be reasonable and fit into the game's setting. This is a roleplay server first and foremost, so give your character the effort it deserves.

## 5.1 Naming

    - Avoid names of locations, brands, fictional/real people or names parodying them (e.g. Baul Sadman, Tom Ford.)
	- The naming guidelines on Scavstation are far more lax than other MRP servers. Somewhat goofy names (Flameo Hotman, Dr. Dachter, Bitcoin) are acceptable.
	-- HOWEVER. If you choose a goofy name, have some understanding in mind of how they came to be called that (military callsign? spiteful parents?).
	-- Yinglets are particularly lax in terms of allowing goofy names.
	- Direct portrayals of real-world people and fictional characters are not allowed.
    - If you name and design your character the same as a well-known player's character, the default in-character assumption is that you are a variant of them from a parallel universe.
    - All species have a naming convention, be sure to generally follow it. If your character's displayed name is a "Nickname", have their actual legal name handy.

## 5.2 Roleplay Standards

    - Treat your character as a separate entity from you, the player.
    -- Your character's actions and feelings in-game should be based solely on the experiences of the character, not you.
	- Your character should be believable as a real person.
	-- This applies even if your character has a goofy name. Dont be a caricature, you're playing a person with motivations and serious thoughts.
	-- Your character had to have survived long enough to make it this far in life, play them as if they have the presence of mind and self-preservation to have done so.
    - Low roleplay actions that have no regard for your character or the setting (memes, silly copy paste spam IC) are not acceptable.
	- Do not engage in harassment or persistent annoyance of other characters. If someone tells you in LOOC to leave them alone, back off.
    - Do not use Netspeak in in-character chat (i.e. ROFL, XD, FR, IDK). "LOL", "LMAO" and other forms of netspeak commonly spoken aloud IRL are acceptable.
</Document>
