<Document>
# AMBITION-CLASS ATMOSPHERICS PLATFORM
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignEngineering" Caption="Produce"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignAtmos" Caption="Refine"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EngineeringTechFab"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gaslock"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMiningDrill"/>
</Box>
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapAmbition" Caption=""/>
</Box>
[color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Large

[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 4-8

[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Bananium

[color=#a4885c]Base Power Draw:[/color] 81 kW

[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] No

[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

[color=#a4885c]Available Roles:[/color] Contractor, Pilot, Mercenary

"Declassified gas production and distribution platform seized in a hostile takeover of an Atmosian conglomerate. For the ultimate insurgent."

# Piloting
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerShuttle"/>
</Box>
After clicking the shuttle console, you should see a radar view of the shuttle. Here are the steps for piloting the shuttle back and forth:

-First, disconnect any airlocks that are connected to the dock.
-Then, you actually get to pilot the shuttle. The controls are fairly simple, with [color=#028ed9]"W"[/color] and [color=#028ed9]"S"[/color] being forward and backward, [color=#028ed9]"A"[/color] and [color=#028ed9]"D"[/color] being left and right, and [color=#028ed9]"Q"[/color] and [color=#028ed9]"E"[/color] being rotating left and right; and [color=#028ed9]"spacebar"[/color] being the brake and moving precicely by holding the [color=#028ed9]"spacebar"[/color] while doing other inputs.
-For more info on Poloting please read this artical on [textlink="Piloting" link="Piloting"]

# Hiring crew
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerStationRecords"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadsetGrey"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="IntercomCommon"/>
</Box>
As a Captain of a Nanotrasen vessel, you have the authority to hire, fire, demote, or promote crew members at will. There are two ways you as a Captain can go about hiring crew: you can either use the [color=#a4885c]station records computer[/color] on your ship to open crew slots (jobs available vary from ship to ship) or invite through in-game communications other players to your crew.

# PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

## 1. Power supply

## 1.1. Battery units
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
</Box>

- Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
- Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
- Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
- Check the APC unit's current Load (W).

## 1.2. D-K Jr. generator unit
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorDKJr"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FuelBananium"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignRadiation"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterSuitRad"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GeigerCounter"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttersRadiation"/>
</Box>

- Check if the D-K Jr. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
- Check if the D-K Jr. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
- Check if the D-K Jr. generator unit is set to HV output.
- Set Target Power for need to 42 [bold]k[/bold]W on both generators for a maximum of 82 [bold]k[/bold]W.
- Start the D-K Jr. generator unit.
- Close radiation shielding.
Note: Be sure to take all necessary protective measures when working with radioactive materials and environments: use a radiation suit and keep radiation shutters closed at all times.
-For more info on power please read this artical on [textlink="Power" link="Power"].

## 2. Atmospherics

## 2.1. Distribution Loop
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasVentPump"/>
</Box>

- Check if the Oxygen canister is anchored to connector port.
- Check if the Nitrogen canister is anchored to connector port.
- Check if the distribution Mixer Pump is set to normal pressure (101.3kPa).
- Enable the Mixer Pump.
- Anchor gas canisters to Connector Ports as needed if canisters empty.

## 2.2. Waste Loop
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasValve"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasFilter"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasVentScrubber"/>
</Box>

- Enable waste loop pump and valve(s).
- Enable waste loop filters.
- Set appropriate gases for each storage chamber as needed.

For more info on Atmos systems please read more in [textlink="Atmospherics" link="Atmospherics"].

## 3. Other checks
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BlastDoor"/>
</Box>

- Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
- Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
- Check that the blast doors are closed.

 ## 4. Ship Functions

 ## 4.1. Gas Mining
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gaslock"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GaslockFrame"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMiningDrill"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorJrPacman"/>
  </Box>
  The ship comes equipped with all the necessary equipment for Offshore Gas Mining. If you would like to learn the basics please read the article about [textlink="Offshore Gas Mining" link="OffshoreGasMining"].

## Sidenotes

* - Ambition-class atmospheric platforms are equipped with eleven APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. Unmodified Ambition-class ship requires 81 kW of power to remain operational.

</Document>
