<Document>
  # BARBER-CLASS SERVICE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BarberScissors"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SprayBottleSpaceCleaner"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RagItem"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapBarber" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2+

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "The Barber is a medium-sized personal service vessel designed to provide barbers the equipments they need."

  [italic]Brought to you by Shipyard Settler's Shuttle.[/italic]

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the wall substation unit is anchored to the wall.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).

  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacman"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units have fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 13-14** [bold]kW[/bold].
  - Start P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (21% Oxygen, 79% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>

  - Enable waste loop pump.
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarm in the Engine Room.
  - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to Filtering (Wide).

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Barber-class service ships are equipped with one APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption.

  ** - Recommended Target Power value to avoid blackouts during Gravity Generator charging sequence is 14 kW.

</Document>
