<Document>
  # BRIGAND-CLASS EXPEDITION SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingMaskGasMercenary"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponRifleAk"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="IngotGold"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobRandomSecurityCorpse"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapBrigand" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 3-6
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] AME
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] Yes
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
  "Civilian conversion of an old military light frigate from the early days of humanity's expansion to the stars. The original light frigate design was made in pre-FTL era of technology. Manufactured by Langstad-Voigt Heavy Industries."
    
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. AME generator unit.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the AME core is properly shielded.
  - Check that the AME controller unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check the AME controller unit Fuel Status.
  - Check the AME controller unit Injection Amount.
  - Toggle Injection.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (21% Oxygen, 79% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump (located at Cargo Bay).
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BlastDoor"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the blast doors are closed.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Brigand-class expedition shuttles are equipped with three APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. Unmodifued Brigand-class ship requires 27.1 kW of power to remain operational.

</Document>
