<Document>
  # Bullseye-class Recreational Ship
  
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium (31h x 20w)
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-3
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma + Solars
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]Available Roles:[/color] Chef, Botanist.
	
  "A relatively small vessel where someone had the idea to strap a miniature restaurant to a firing range."
  
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  
  - Check if the substation and SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check if the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  
  - Check if the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor and it's magnet is on.
  - Check if the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check if the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 8** [bold]k[/bold]W, if the Solar Panels are not facing the sun what so ever and you can't turn the ship you may need to increase the [bold]k[/bold]W to chase the Network.
  - Start the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  - Keep an eye on the battery % of the substation and SMES as time passes.
  
  ##1.3 Solar generator unit
  - Check if the Solar Control Console is anchored to the floor.
  - With vaccum protection, check if the Solar Panels are anchored to the floor.
  - With vaccum protection, check of the Solar Tracker is anchored to the floor.
  - On the Solar Control Console, set the Panel Angular Velocity to 6.4 or 6.5, and match the Panel Angle to the Sun Angle.
  - If the Panel Angle isn't matching the Sun Angle over time as they increase, adjust the Velocity accordingly to keep them aligned.
  - Make sure the Solar Panels have direct view to the sun and aren't obstructed by your ship. 
  - If out of power, use the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit until you can turn the ship towards the sun to recharge.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  - Check if the air canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check if the gas pump below the air canister is on.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarm in the Engine Room.
  - Set air alarm filtering to wide.
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  
  - With vaccum protection, check if the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - With vaccum protection, check if the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check if all the kitchen appliances are anchored to the floor/tables.
  - Check if the seed extractor is anchored to the floor.
  - Check if the material reclaimer is anchored to the floor and it's magnet is on.
  - Check if the conveyer belt leading to the material reclaimer is on and moving the correct direction via the lever above it.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Bullseye-class recreational ships are equipped with a single APC unit that can be used to appraise twhe ship's total power consumption (16.1 kW). One can check the ship's total power consumption against the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit Target Power output: to keep substation and APC fully charged, P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit Target Power output should exceed APC's Load. Remember to check APC Load and adjust the generator unit Target Power after connecting new power-consuming machines.
  
  ** - Bullseye-class recreational ships have varying power demand meaning that standard P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit's Target Power value can be lowered as low as 7 kW up as high as 15 kW when recharging the power units. Please note, during the event of your power units being fully spent, the recommended Target Power value on your P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit during the Gravity Generator charging sequence is 25 kW. Its then suggested when power comes back on you should make sure the Solar Panels are set to face the correct direction on your Solar Control Computer and aren't obstructed by your ship, then turn your ship so the Solar Panels aren't obstructed. Then once your power units are sufficently charged lower the target kW back down to the appropriate value. If you have no fuel remaining, request assistance on the radio.

</Document>
