<Document>
  # CALADRIUS-CLASS HOSPITAL SHUTTLE
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerMedical" Caption="Restore"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFPosterContrabandFsbLogo" Caption="Research"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerEngineering" Caption="Recover"/>    
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapCaladrius" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Large

  [color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 5-10

  [color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] AME

  [color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] No

  [color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "The Caladrius is the Far Star Biotech Corporation's premier expeditionary medical carrier. Designed for large scale colonization support, humanitarian relief and post-disaster investigation and recovery operations.

  As a medical carrier your primary mission is to provide for the physical and mechanical needs of your stationed sector by direct intervention or through dispatch of appropriate crews to sites of distress. The Caladrius is at its strongest when serving as a logistics hub to manage multiple cases.

  Your secondary mission is to investigate spaceborne wrecks, attempt recovery of Nanotrasen contracted assets where possible and repurpose any recoverable derelict materials to extend the operational life of your vessel.

  The Caladrius depends on the coordination and utilization of its crew. With each station filled the vessel becomes a commanding presence in the void. Capable of responding to nearly any emergency be it medical or engineering."
  
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorCMO" Caption="Chief Medical Officer"/>
</Box>
The Chief Medical Officer of a Far Star Biotech craft is charged with ensuring the smooth operation of the vessel, the assigning of roles and the provision of guidance, training and crew retention and satisfaction and in adhering to corporate directives as they arise. Keep your crew happy, keep them fed, keep them alive. Unless dictated otherwise by the mission.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorParamedic" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFSignEms2" Caption="Medical Staff"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorMedicalDoctor" Caption=""/>
</Box>
The medics ensure that the medical floor of the Caladrius is prepepped and ready to respond to emergencies. They serve as health providers both at home and through distant response utilizing dispatch shuttles.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorChemist" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignChem" Caption="Medical Supply Staff"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorBotanist" Caption=""/>
</Box>
The chemist is responsible for producing medical materials such as topicals, chemicals and pens, employed by medics and sector employees. The fabrication of goods and the the hydroponics bay is their domain.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorSalvageSpecialist" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignSalvage" Caption="Material Supply Staff"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorCargoTechnician" Caption=""/>
</Box>
The engineers and salvage technicians are charged with providing repair support to damaged vessels and in performing salvage operations to ensure that the Caladrius has the materials and means to produce the tools needed for it to do its job. The fabrication of machine parts, maintenance of the atmospheric and engineering systems are their domains.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorLawyer" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignPsychology" Caption="Crew and Patient Support Staff"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RandomHumanoidVisitorChaplain" Caption=""/>
</Box>
All support staff such as psychologists, chaplains and civilian sector jobs where appropriate defer to the roles and assignments assigned by the Chief Medical Officer commanding. The wellbeing and morale of the crew is their domain."

# SHIP OPERATION AND TOOLS

## 1. Hangar Systems

<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CaladriusMothershipComputer" Caption="Mothership Console"/>
</Box>

As a carrier a limited number of support vessels are available to you to fulfill your mission. The assemble and prepare controls for these craft are located on the bridge.

## 2. Controls

<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCautionSecurity" Caption=""/>
</Box>
  Security framed controls are responsible for bolting airlocks. A master security control is located on the bridge and secondary controls are located in the cargo, power and atmospheric wings.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCaution" Caption=""/>
</Box>
  Caution framed controls are responsible for bulkheads permitting passage into the void and for large scale power management. Thruster controls are located in the generator wing.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameGrey" Caption=""/>
</Box>
  Standard framed controls are responsible for controlling shutters and should be activated for purposes of privacy or in the event that shuttle windows show signs of structural distress or destruction.

## 3. Engineering Wing

<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignEngineering" Caption=""/>
</Box>

The engineering wing contains your primary SMES banks and shielded generator room. The stock Caladrius comes equipped with a baseline AME generator unit. Under the careful supervision of a engineering professional this power system may be modified as the mission and tools available become available.
The engineering wing also contains your master thruster control panel. In the event that the vessel requires additional banked power the vessel's thrust systems may be powered down via the caution paneled button adjacent to the power monitoring station.

## 4. Atmospherics Wing

<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignAtmos" Caption=""/>
</Box>

The atmospherics wing contains the stock gas reserves available to the Caladrius in addition to space provided for gas seperation and storage. Trained atmospheric technicians are provided with the tools needed to seperate and store gasses as available to both preserve exotic samples as per FSB directive, isolate pathogens or to extend mission the mission's lifetime.

# PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

## 1. Power supply

## 1.1. Battery units
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. AME generator unit.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the AME core is properly shielded.
  - Check that the AME controller unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check the AME controller unit Fuel Status.
  - Check the AME controller unit Injection Amount.
  - Toggle Injection.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (21% Oxygen, 79% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump (located in the atmospherics bay.).
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BlastDoor"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the blast doors are closed.


</Document>
