<Document>
  # CERES-CLASS SERVICE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="KitchenKnife"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="KitchenMicrowave"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="KitchenElectricGrill"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapCeres" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

  [color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-4

  [color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Uranium

  [color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

  [color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A medium-size, high-class restaurant ship with ample seating, integrated botany and a dining room for VIP guests."

  [italic]Brought to you by BlueBird Starship Design & Construction.[/italic]

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC units' Main Breakers are toggled on.
  - Check the APC units' current Load (W).

  ## 1.2. S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorSuperPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is fueled. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation.
  - Check that S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power to 24 [bold]kW[/bold] on the generator unit.
  - Start S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the oxygen and nitrogen canisters are anchored to the connector port.
  - Check that the distribution mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable the distribution mixer.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>

  - Enable waste loop pump.
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarm in the Engine Room.
  - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to Filtering (Wide).

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  # GETTING THE MOST OUT OF THE CERES

  - The Ceres is designed for multi-person crews. Consider having a dedicated botanist to grow quality produce.
  - Though unorthodox, the disposal units are designed to safely and efficiently transport produce from botany to kitchen. Make use of them!
  - Don't be afraid to adjust the table and seating layout to suit your needs.
  - For serving food to a larger party, the food carts in the freezer may simplify transportation.
</Document>
