<Document>
    # EAGLE-CLASS MEDICAL SHUTTLE
    <Box>
      <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerCrewMonitoring"/>
      <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RollerBed"/>
      <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="StasisBed"/>
	  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ChemMaster"/>
    </Box>
    <Box>
      <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapEagle" Caption=""/>
    </Box>
  
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

    [color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-4

    [color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Uranium

    [color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

    [color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

    "A modern, medium-sized medical & engineering vessel. Focusing on responding to shuttle distress, Eagle bears the motto 'Recover, Restore, Repair!'."

    # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

    ## 1. Power supply

    ## 1.1. Battery units
    <Box>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
    </Box>

    - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
    - Check the substation unit.
    - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
    - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).

    ## 1.2. S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units
    <Box>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorSuperPacman"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetUranium"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignRadiationMed"/>
    </Box>

   - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are anchored to the floor.
   - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units have fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
   - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are set to HV output.
   - Set Target Power for 16 [bold]k[/bold]W.
   - Start the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

     ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
    <Box>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
    </Box>

    - Check if the O2 canister and N2 canister are anchored to their connector ports.
    - Check if the gas mixer has its mixing ratio and output pressure set correctly.
    - Enable the gas mixer.

    ## 2.2. Waste Loop
    <Box>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
    </Box>

    - Check waste loop pump.
    - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to Filtering (Wide).

    ## 3. Other checks
    <Box>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
        <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttersRadiation"/>
    </Box>

    - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
    - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
    - Check that radiation shutters are closed.

    ## Sidenotes

    * - Eagle-class medical response ships are equipped with several APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption (which for the unmodified ship is 15.7 kW). To keep the substation and APC fully charged, the generator target power should exceed APC's Load, but by as little as possible to achieve maximum fuel efficiency. Remember to check the APC Load and adjust the generator unit's target power after adding or removing power-consuming machines.

    ** - Eagle-class ships have a slightly above average power demand. A standard P.A.C.M.A.N. generator's target power value can be set to 15-16 kW to modulate between drain and charge. As much of the powerdraw is to sustain the chemistry lab powering down those machines can dramatically reduce the ship's overall draw.

</Document>
