<Document>
# FIRAMEQ-CLASS CARGO PSEUDO-STATION
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateTradeSecureNormal" Caption="Buy"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MechEmuCargo" Caption="Sort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BannerCargo" Caption="Sell"/>
</Box>
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapFirameq" Caption=""/>
</Box>

[color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Large

[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-6

[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Solar

# Shuttle Brief

"The Firameq (First Amongst Equals) is a cargo sorting pseudo-station, designed by MacroSol Shipyards to be parked outside of the 200m traffic control zone of trade stations, and assist in sorting cargo for bulk haulers. Intended as a core node of local trade, the Firameq has an on-board office for financial reporting. The Firameq is a highly specialised craft, and is primarily recommended for experienced captains." 

# Ship Functions
[color=#a4885c]Bridge[/color]
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCautionSecurity" Caption="Bolt Sale Airlocks"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameGrey" Caption="Toggle Thrusters/Gyro"/>
</Box>

[color=#a4885c]Sales[/color]
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCautionSecurity" Caption="Bolt Sale Airlocks"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameGrey" Caption="Toggle Airlock/Blast Doors"/>
</Box>

[color=#a4885c]Entire Craft[/color]
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="LockableButtonEngineering" Caption="Open Emergency Shutters"/>
</Box>

# Recommended Use

The Firameq is a highly specialised craft, meant to facilitate a sector's trade efficiency. As such, its use may be unfamiliar to traditional cargo hauling captains. Upon purchase of a Firameq-class Pseudo-station, one is recommended to first array the Solar Panels such that they follow the sun. 
Though an unmodified Firameq can last at least a quarter of an hour without aligned solar panels, MacroSol Interstellar(MacroSol Int.) recommends proactive alignment to avoid stranding. The next recommended step, is to travel outside of the Traffic Control radius of the nearest trade station and park there for the duration of service.

MacroSol Int. recommends a minimum skeleton crew of two, and at least a single small cargo vessel of your choice. This small cargo vessel should ferry cargo from the nearest trade station, to the fore cargo-hold at the In Docks, where the cargo can be unloaded. Then, the cargo should be sorted by destination in the main cargo bay. Sorted cargo can be loaded into the appropriately lettered sale racks, where customers can receive them, without gaining undue access to your main cargo hold. Safe and Secure.

Then, customers should be invited to dock with the appropriate Out Docks, where the sorted cargo can be sold for a modest profit by the rack-load, for these pioneering captains to fly true, without diversion.

Repeat, and profit.

May you form the keystone that supports trade in your sector, and good luck.

 # Cargo

  [textlink="Cargo Hauling" link="CargoHauling"/]

  # Piloting

  [textlink="Piloting" link="Piloting"/]

  [textlink="Sector Topology" link="SectorTopology"/]

  # Hiring crew

  [textlink="Hiring" link="Hiring"/]

  As a Captain of a Nanotrasen vessel, you have the authority to hire, fire, demote, or promote crew members at will.

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  [textlink="Preflight Checklist" link="PreflightChecklist"/]

</Document>