<Document>
  # HONKER-CLASS CLOWN SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineTheater"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="StatueBananiumClown"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateToyBox"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapHonker" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Small
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1-2
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
  "HONK HONK HONK HONK HONK HONK"
    
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 9-10** [bold]kW[/bold].
  - Ensure that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is enabled.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the Air canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Ensure that the distro loop pump is enabled.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Ensure that the waste loop pump is enabled.
  - Disable Auto Mode on any Air Alarms.
  - Set the Air Alarms to Filtering (Wide).
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Honker-class clown ships are equipped with an APC unit that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. An unmodified Honker-class ship requires 8.4 kW of power to remain operational.
  
  ** - Honker-class clown ships have low power demand meaning that standard P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit's Target Power value can be lowered as low as 9 kW. Please note, that recommended Target Power value to avoid blackouts during Gravity Generator charging sequence is 10 kW.

</Document>
