<Document>
  # KESTREL-CLASS SALVAGE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MiningDrill"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OreBag"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineSalvage"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RipleyChassis"/>
  </Box>  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapKestrel" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Small
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-4
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Uranium
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
  "Once a local shipping lane freighter, this model has been converted for use in debris field mining and salvage operations."
    
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorSuperPacman"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetUranium"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignRadiationMed"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check that the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 29-30** [bold]kW[/bold].
  - Start the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (21% Oxygen, 79% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump.
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BlastDoor"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the blast doors are closed.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Kestrel-class salvage ships are equipped with five APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. Unmodifued Kestrel-class ship requires 28.6 kW of power to remain operational.
  
  ** - Kestrel-class salvage ships have higher power demand than a standard P.A.C.M.A.N. can provide at optimal settings, and come equipped with a S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. instead. Please note that the recommended Target Power value to avoid blackouts during Gravity Generator charging sequence is 30 kW.
  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignRadiationMed"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingOuterSuitRad"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GeigerCounter"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttersRadiation"/>
  </Box>
  Note: Be sure to take all necessary protective measures when working with radioactive materials: use a radiation suit, engage internals, make sure to enable Geiger's counter, wash your hands after, and keep radiation shutters closed at all times.

</Document>
