<Document>
  # LANTERN-CLASS SERVICE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineChapel"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Bible"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingNeckCrucifix"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Censer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="UrnMortuary"/>
  </Box>  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadHatWitchhunter"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WoodenStake"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Torch"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrossbowImprovised"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapLantern" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-3
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Solar/Plasma
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
  "A medium-sized shuttle to promote your religion. Manufactured by Langstad-Voigt Heavy Industries."
    
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 12-14** [bold]kW[/bold].
  - Start the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  
  ## 1.3. Solar panels
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerSolarControl"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SolarTracker"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SolarPanel"/>
  </Box>
  - Inspect solar control computer (located at shuttle cockpit).
  - Adjust panel angular velocity.
  - Adjust panel angle.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the air canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the distribution pump is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable the distribution pump.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump.
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarm in the Engine Room.
  - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to Filtering (Wide).
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Lantern-class service ships are equipped with three APC units that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption. Unmodifued Lantern-class ship requires 22.5 kW of power to remain operational.
  
  ** - Lantern-class service ships have higher power demand than standard P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit can provide at optimal settings, however the ship comes equipped with 38 solar panels that can provide up to 28.5 kW of power under the ideal circumstances: assuming that on average properly maintained solar array will provide one third of maximum output power, recommended target power output for P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is 14 kW.

</Document>
