<Document>
  # PIONEER-CLASS SALVAGE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MiningDrill"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OreBag"/>
  </Box>  
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapPioneer" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Small (Micro)
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
  "A cargo container outfitted to be space-capable and equipped for salvaging and mining, either on its own, or as part of a fleet. Manufactured by Langstad-Voigt Heavy Industries."
    
  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationWallBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).
  
  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check that the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power to 5-6** [bold]kW[/bold].
  - Start the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the air canister is anchored to connector port.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump.
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarm in the Engine Room.
  - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to Filtering (Wide).
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SmallGyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttersWindow"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the bow window shutters are closed.
  
  ## Sidenotes
  
  * - Pioneer-class salvage ships are equipped with a single APC unit that can be used to appraise the ship's total power consumption (4.6 kW). One can check the ship's total power consumption against the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit Target Power output: to keep substation and APC fully charged, P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit Target Power output should exceed APC's Load. Remember to check APC Load and adjust the generator unit Target Power after connecting new power-consuming machines.
  
  ** - Pioneer-class salvage ships have low power demand meaning that standard P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit's Target Power value can be lowered as low as 5 kW. Please note, that recommended Target Power value to avoid blackouts during Gravity Generator charging sequence is 6 kW.

</Document>
