<Document>
  # SAKURATSU-CLASS SALVAGE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponProtoKineticAccelerator"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ResearchAndDevelopmentServer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MiningDrill"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OreProcessor"/>
  </Box>  
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium
	
	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-5
	
	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma
	
	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None
	
	[color=#a4885c]Available Roles:[/color] Contractor, Pilot, Mercenary
	
  "The Sakuratsu is a shuttle that has capabilities for salvage, and light cargo transport. The ship is also equipped with a research console and server."

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST
  
  ## 1. Power supply
  
  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>
  
    - Check if the APC units are charged.
    - Check if all APC units are toggled on.
  
  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check if the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units is anchored to the floor.
  - Check if the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 20** [bold]k[/bold]W on all 3.
  - Start the P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units.
  
  ## 2. Atmospherics
  
  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Check if the canisters for oxygen and nitrogen is anchored to the ports in the engineering section of the ship.
  - Check if the distribution pump is set to normal pressure (101kPa).
  - Enable the distribution pump.
  - If swapping canisters for distro, ensure that the nitrogen/oxygen mix is at 78/22 with the gas mixer.
  
  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>
    
  - Enable waste loop pump.
  - Disable Auto Mode on the Air Alarms around the ship.
  - Set the Air Alarm in the Engine Room to FILTERING.
  - If there is a dangerous gas in the atmosphere, set the Air Alarm in the room to PANIC.
  - If a room is lacking sufficient atmosphere, set the Air Alarm in the room to FILL.
  
  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check if the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check if the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Sakuratsu-class ships are fitted with canister filling rooms. This will be the room with the door in atmos colors. This is NOT a second distro.

  ** - The door for the salvage bay is on the right side of the rear. This is the only dedicated door for salvage on the ship.

  *** - The max power the generators can provide is 75** [bold]k[/bold]W, this is not recommended however, as this will be quite ineffecient.

</Document>
