<Document>
  # INFINITE OCEAN INDUSTRIES SHARKBAIT EXPEDITION SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerTelevision" Caption="Entertainment"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComfyChair" Caption="Comfort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MercenaryTechFab" Caption="Combat And Glory" />
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapSharkbait" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-3

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] AME

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] Yes

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A 3 person exploration vessel designed to spend months in space in relative comfort. This vessel was once the height of luxury but now compared to more modern options it's the perfect budget vessel for an adventure."

  # Tips on running the IOI Sharkbait
  - Optimal [bold]Target Power[/bold] (kW) for the generator unit is [color=#a4885c]30.5[bold]kW[/bold][/color]. The shuttle comes with large EVA access in the tail fins and a large cargo/salvage bay to accomadate your trinkets and other belongings. There are 3 beds for a 3 person crew so everyone can have their own bed for maximum comfort.
  - Almost every room is equipped with a button that is lined with black and yellow, these buttons will control the shutters for the rooms they are within. The red and black lined button located within the bridge controls the thrusters power, allowing you to relax anywhere you wish without having to worry about spending unnecesary power. Near the tail EVA access is a shuttle safe and a weapon rack to store your weapons for ease of access. In the middle of the ship is a room designed after a "living room" from Terra era housing, it has all your entertainment needs for those long journeys across the galaxy.
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCautionSecurity" Caption="Toggle Thrusters"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameCaution" Caption="Toggle Shutters"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ButtonFrameGrey" Caption="Toggle Airlock Bolts"/>
  </Box>
  - Refer to [textlink="Piloting" link="Piloting"] if you wish to understand how commandeering a vessel works.
  - For the basics of [bold]expedition diving[/bold], refer to [textlink="Expeditions" link="Expeditions"].
  - If you wish to have company while exploreing the stars you may hire crew aboard. [textlink="Hiring" link="Hiring"]

</Document>
