<Document>
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherDagger" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherAxe" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherGlaive" Caption=""/>
</Box>
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherDaggerAdvanced" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherAxeAdvanced" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherGlaiveAdvanced" Caption=""/>
</Box>
To bind a shade - drawn thin and trembling from beyond the veil - to the edge of a crusher-type weapon is no simple undertaking, nor one to be approached without a measured hand and a resolute will. The rite demands patience, precision, and a willingness to tread the narrow boundary between the seen and the unseen. What follows are the prescribed steps, set down not merely as instruction, but as a solemn progression of acts through which the binding may be achieved.

# 1.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TableWood" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AltarFangs" Caption=""/>
</Box>
First, prepare the space. Select a surface that is even, steady, and free from disturbance, for any imbalance may disrupt the delicate tether you are about to forge. If fortune allows, let this place be an altar - something consecrated or at least set apart - so that the act carries with it the quiet gravity it deserves.

# 2.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShardCrystalRed" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Next, take the red crystal shard and lodge it firmly into position nearby. This shard is no mere ornament; it serves as a beacon, a signal cast into the unseen depths, calling to the wandering shade and guiding it toward the locus of the ritual.

# 3.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Bloodpack" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Then comes the offering. The glaive itself must be anointed - no, fully covered - in blood. This is not done lightly, for the entity you seek to bind must be appeased, coaxed into cooperation by a gesture it understands. Let the blade drink deeply, until it gleams with the crimson promise of the pact.

# 4.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ScrollCultShadeBinding" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Finally, steady your voice and your mind, and recite the incantation exactly as it is written within the shade-binding scroll. Each word is a thread, each syllable a knot; together they form the tether that will draw the shade from the veil and fasten it, irrevocably, to the weapon before you.

Proceed without haste, and without error - for once begun, such rites are seldom forgiving.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherDaggerBloodCult" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherAxeBloodCult" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NFWeaponCrusherGlaiveBloodCult" Caption=""/>
</Box>
</Document>
