<Document>
# On the Awakening of an Inert Arcane Staff
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponInertStaffCultistBoltDark"/>
</Box>
At times, after prolonged and tireless use, the crystals set within adept-level cult staves will grow dim - veiled in soot and rendered inert, their once eager responsiveness dulled to silence. Such a condition is neither uncommon nor irreversible, though it must be addressed with care. To restore the staff to its proper function, one must proceed as follows.

## 1.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShardCrystalRed"/>
</Box>
First, obtain a fresh red crystal shard to serve as a suitable replacement. Remove the dulled and sullied fragment, and in its stead set the new shard, pressing it firmly into the socket until it rests secure and unyielding, as though it had always belonged there.

## 2.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Bloodpack"/>
</Box>
Second, the staff must be rededicated. In the name of Nar'Sie, it is to be bathed in blood - an offering both symbolic and binding. Should the rite require steadiness or sanctity, lay the staff upon an altar, allowing the act to take on the full weight of ritual observance.

<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponChargedStaffCultistBoltDarkAdept"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="StaffRechargerCult"/>
</Box>

# On the Ascension of an Adept's Staff to Mastery
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponChargedStaffCultistBoltDarkAdept"/>
</Box>
Upon attaining true mastery over the art of blood magic, it becomes not only fitting but necessary that one's staff be elevated in kind, its form and function brought into harmony with the wielder's ascended state. Such an augmentation is neither trivial nor without risk, and thus must be undertaken with deliberate care.

# 1.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AnomalyCoreBluespace" Caption=""/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AnomalyCoreFlesh" Caption="anomaly core"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AnomalyCoreElectricity" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Begin by securing an anomaly core, whether dormant or still faintly alive with residual force; either will suffice, provided it remains intact. This core shall serve as the catalyst for the staff's transformation.

With both implements prepared, bring the core into union with the staff's crystal, guiding the fusion with steady hands and an unwavering will. As the two begin to merge, you must recite the Eighth Rite of Sanguine Glory, each word spoken with precision and intent, lest the process falter. In this convergence of object, voice, and purpose, the staff will shed its former limitations and emerge as a reflection of its master's power.
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponChargedStaffCultistBoltDarkMaster"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="StaffRechargerCult"/>
</Box>
</Document>
